I don't want to wait one more minute.
I'm ready now.
And I'm gonna play now.
Dude, I realized I'm the same with my microwave.
You know, I put the microwave at three minutes and I'm like standing there.
Okay, come on, let's go.
I'm watching it count down and when it's at like 20 seconds, I'm like, fuck, what's 20 seconds gonna do?
I always cancel it at 20 seconds and take the food out.
Those 20 seconds are the longest 20 seconds of all time.
I don't want to wait 20 seconds.
You know what I mean?
Then it's always cold in the middle.
That's fine.
It is what it is.
I just, God, just standing there and looking at, you know, I'm drinking something called Faxacondi Limonel zero calories.
It's quite delicious.
It's like a Danish soda pop type drink.
I guess the closest thing would be Sprite, probably, that you would know.
It's like a lemonade flavored version with no calories, pretty much.
It's pretty good.
It's nice and refreshing.
Scalding hot on the outside, cold in the middle.
That's exactly how it is.
12.562 gigawatts nuclear reactors.
That's, that's, that's kind of crazy, bro.
Man, I miss my, my, uh, I miss my air fryer.
I broke it like over a year ago and I've been missing it ever since.
There's just so many good use cases for an air fryer, you know?
I don't want to use my oven for like one piece of bread.
Then again, even an air fryer is too much for like one piece of bread, but you know what I mean.
I guess I should get a toaster is what I'm saying.
Because I always have cheese on toast in the morning with a black coffee.
And I heat up an entire fucking oven just to heat up that one toast.
Sometimes it's two toasts.
I even had three once.
What's up, natalists?
I like your little NASA mark.
Why do you have that?
What is that even?
NASA Artemis 2.
Oh, I guess you watched Artemis 2 or something?
Maybe I have that too.
Although I probably watched it on YouTube.
Air fryer is god tier when I have the munchies.
Yeah, I agree.
I used to buy like little pieces of, well, sandwich type bread.
And then I would put like cheese on, some tomato sauce, and some basil.
And you could just make a little tiny pizza.
In like no time.
Like a little sandwich pizza thing.
It's amazing.
I would put little pepperonis on it if I had it, you know?
Very nice.
I'm doing great today.
Thank you, Beth.
How about you?
I'm in a fantastic mood.
And just one of those days.
I was gonna stream at three, but man, I was ready now, you know?
Like, I'm sorry.
I kind of like these little earlier streams lately.
I just feel more energized to play games at this time.
It's, it's, yeah.
It is what it is.
An air knifer?
I'm down with that, Mitch.
Maybe you can invent that.
The streamable legendary?
Wait, who shared the script with you?
How do you know?
How did you gain access?
Who authorized this?
Someone posted a meme on the Discord channel some days ago.
I forgot the exact wording, but it was something like, what to say when you meet her dad.
And, dude, that made me laugh for so long.
And one of the things was like, uh, the questions, you know, were, so how long have you been her dad?
Or, who authorized this staircase?
And, what else was there?
Uh, I forgot what it was.
Or maybe it wasn't on the Discord.
I saw it somewhere online.
It was just so funny, man.
I could just imagine that, you know, like, it's so stupid.
I have considered playing Satisfactory.
Andromeda Finch, cool name.
But I also want to play Factorio.
And Factorio is apparently the OG, right?
You want to play that before you play, uh, the other game.
Because you start in 2D, and then you transition into 3D, you know?
And it's going to be more mind-blowing, I guess.
What do you say when you meet his dad?
Uh, I don't know.
Probably the same things.
You say, nice beard you got there, dude.
So, what kind of internet connection you got?
Or, so what's on the, what's on the grill?
Like, I wouldn't even want to be with someone whose dad doesn't have a high-speed internet connection, you know what I mean?
That's, that's where I draw the line.
What games do you play?
Oh, you're not asking me.
You're asking the questions you would ask the dad of a hypothetical person you're dating.
I'm playing all kinds of games, man, as is evident lately.
I'm playing everything from Minecraft to StarCraft to World of Warcraft.
I guess it's all craft games, isn't it?
Damn.
And Doki Doki Literature Club, I play that shit too.
I play it all.
I have no limits.
I will try everything.
Will I like it though?
I don't know about that.
Let's play some Minecraft.
And by the way, I actually did leave the game running a little bit.
I swear this isn't scripted.
I guess I died.
Fucking hell.
A skeleton?
But I have lights every...
Wait, where's my...
I don't even know my way around my house.
This way.
The plan was to leave the game running so that these sheep would multiply.
Dude, this feels so scripted.
It's not.
I promise you, this is real.
I have no idea how that skeleton got me, I guess.
I...
But it's fine.
I mean, whatever.
Not a big deal.
Didn't I lose something else?
What about my shoes?
Oh, there, there.
Okay.
And then we do this one here, that one there.
So, let me see.
How many did you make?
Dude, you haven't even duplicated!
What is this shit?
Oh, there's no wheat on the machine.
Oh, did I even fill it up with the wheat?
Am I an idiot?
Ah, man.
Oh wait, we've got wheat here.
You know, okay, you know what, actually, regarding the food?
I...
Okay, I...
We're gonna do it the old-fashioned way.
I'm gonna make a huge-ass proper farm with a lot of animals.
Because if you think about it, I don't need many cycles of feeding to multiply them into infinity, you know?
Powers of two are strong, man.
Actually, powers of ten.
Powers of two.
You know what I mean.
We doubled it, right?
Cooked mutton go in my mouth.
And there's this...
Why is this music always playing when I have sadness happening in my life?
And when I say my life, I mean Minecraft.
Minecraft is my life.
Let me see here.
Oh, right, yeah.
I'm too damn greedy.
No one to stop.
We need a checklist of items before going on expeditions.
Yeah, we definitely need that.
At some point.
Not right now.
Fill this up.
Uh, we're gonna make a proper farm.
I've had it.
With these goddamn snakes on this plane.
You know?
Enough is enough!
It's time to open some windows.
Maybe I'll even get some leads.
So we can collect some cows and sheep and shit.
You know?
Uh, where would a good spot be for the farm?
We're gonna make a proper one.
Uh, well, honestly, it's not great right here.
It's too not flat, you know what I mean?
Hmm.
Interesting.
Perhaps over here.
Near the water-ish.
Let's just start.
We're gonna do like this.
Obviously, that's ugly over there.
We're gonna fix that at some point.
We're gonna start with a naive, uh, square.
Hey, you know what?
I don't mind there being trees inside of here.
That's kind of nice for the cows.
I also...
Honestly, this is one of the reasons I'm doing this.
I feel kind of bad for the cows.
Like, I don't want to put the cows and the sheep inside a tiny, tiny enclosure.
And have them just die.
You know?
Because of that.
We're gonna give them a good life.
I know it's just a game, but man, it's...
It's tough on my psyche.
I can't do that.
I can't.
I tried, okay?
And when it comes to it, I bet I can't even pollute the ocean even if I want to.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I don't have a shield on me.
That's fine.
I don't need a shield.
I'm gonna murder this guy.
Also, today we're getting full netherite.
We have the full setup.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, I have exactly enough?
That's crazy.
Dude, I have the exact amount of fence and one single gate.
The hell?
Isn't that kind of unheard of?
Let's make the entrance over here.
I feel like that's super unlikely, you know?
Did I just get hit by that arrow?
No.
There we go.
Look at this.
We're gonna have a...
Dude, let's have a little pond in here, too.
All the animals are gonna be so happy.
Where's my shovel?
This song is a perfect reflection of my mental state right now.
Okay.
Let's go get some animals, shall we?
In fact, I have wheat here.
Guys, you're free.
No more torment.
Come with me.
To better lands.
You're not gonna get poked by the poking machine anymore.
Matt is actually so fucked up.
What was I thinking making this?
This is much better.
Come here.
Get inside.
Come on.
The whole family goes.
Oh, come on.
You know, you can get in here.
Are you too fat?
Come on.
And...
Yes.
Let's go.
There we go.
Look at this.
I know you love it in here.
There you go.
Let me feed you all.
And you're protected against...
You're actually not protected against zombies because there's a little thingy there.
They can actually get in.
We can't let the wolves get inside the hen house, as they say.
There we go.
Oh, you spawned in here, did you?
How is that possible?
Don't I have lights?
Let's put one more.
Maybe one over here, too.
We gotta take this tree out.
And these.
It was ugly anyway, so...
That's right, you can't get in, son.
Look how happy they are.
They're all, like, meeing and playing and stuff.
Usually the sheep don't make...
Did you notice how the sheep didn't make any of those noises over here?
But now they do.
That means they're happy.
I did the right thing.
God, I feel so good about myself.
We're gonna remove this monstrosity of a contraption.
None of this.
Nuh-uh.
I'm not evil.
I'm very moral.
I take care of the animals.
I mean, I'm gonna kill them, but...
Until then, you know?
Like, I'm not perfect.
I'll be the first to admit it.
I'm just a guy living his life.
But I will kill them.
I will murder them.
I'm gonna go empty my inventory here.
We gotta do it fast before items disappear.
Man, what is that freaking item cult or thingy that makes me able to...
Disenchant and get, you know, things?
I don't know.
Miscellaneous Iron Nuggets and Leavers.
The title of an album.
That is coming out soon.
Lapis Lazuli.
Goes in here.
Nice.
We got some wheat.
Uh, let's go pick up some stuff.
All the chains, we gotta pick them up too.
What's that?
Oh, it's the stuff I threw away.
And then maybe after this, after we get the food situation sorted, like, for real this time.
Maybe I'll just take another look at everything we can craft.
There's still things I haven't experimented with, so we're just gonna try some things.
And then we're gonna go in the nether, of course.
And start digging with the new amazing machine that we have.
Also, it's a little too dark here, I think.
Like, I think enemies can spawn.
Gantry shafts!
Uh, put those in there.
We don't need this right now, or that.
Rails.
Uh, let's put those in redstone.
Yeah.
One bucket.
Uh, I think I'll carry that around.
Minecart with furnace belongs in here.
So, this is, uh, the thing we use together with this.
And where is this contraption that I had with me?
The entire digging machine.
Where did I leave that?
Maybe it is the...
Maybe it is just this thing I just put in there.
Wait, is it actually just that one?
No, no, it would say something like contraption.
Wait, what's that doing there?
That belongs in here.
Look at all this copper!
Experience incoming.
Oh, you know what?
Actually, let's, um...
Let's take this temporarily.
We're gonna take some hoppers.
We're gonna create a little machine that creates experience for us here.
Um...
Yeah.
So, we're gonna have a chest.
I actually have that.
Yep.
And then this one.
Like that.
On top of that, we're gonna have this one.
Facing the other way.
If I can.
Like that.
A little scuffed.
It's temporary.
Don't worry about it.
Fill this bastard up fully.
Uh...
Put the coal in there.
And this will now produce a lot of experience for me.
Isn't that lovely?
I think it is.
Quick and dirty, but it works.
Okay, now, for the cows.
Uh, let's actually go find some cows.
We're gonna get this process started.
Maybe I'll go quickly feed these sheep again.
Do you like your new home?
They must be so happy to be in here.
Oh, it feels so much better.
I actually...
I'm not even gonna lie.
Like, when I was doing the thing last time, I felt so bad.
I didn't say it, but like, inside of me, I was dying, man.
This makes me so happy.
I like this way more.
This brings me happiness.
Oh, we're gonna connect it with the path.
Oh, we're gonna make a path like that.
Oh, oh, it's beautiful.
Very nice.
Okay, um, next up.
Maybe I'll check it.
Okay, hold on.
Let's try and figure out what this freaking machine is that disenchants.
Let me just look in here, I guess.
Because I would really love to do that.
If it's not too much to ask.
Speed-o-meter, uh, could be interesting to make as well at some point.
You know what?
I should be writing down the things that I want to make that I haven't made yet, but can't make as of right now, or don't want to.
You know what I mean, right?
Wait, what is this?
A visual diagram with detailed information about a simulated contraption.
When right-click on simulated contraption, visualize forces acting on the simulated contraption.
Really?
Okay.
But let's not get distracted by that right now.
I'm looking for the vanilla block here.
Dude, I just got an idea for a humane way to collect food from these animals.
It's actually genius.
We, we, uh, we use the weighted ejector, right?
We put it like here or something.
And we somehow filter so that only the adults can go on it.
The big ones get flung up in the air and land on a drill.
Maybe outside of the enclosure.
You know, it's like, oh, you've got, you've reached a certain age now.
Now it's time to die.
You know, we only slaughter those that are 80 or above.
You know, it's, it's...
That was human years for a comparison, but you know what I mean.
And, and that would be like really effective because that way they step on the ejector.
They are going to go to a very specific spot and that is pre-ordained, right?
That is one way to do it.
I mean, it's, I'm saying instead of me having to walk in there with my axe and just go like, you know, on everybody.
The question is, how do we make the filter that only takes adults, not kids?
You know, that's, that's the tricky one, I guess.
Okay, uh, this is all looking good.
We're getting experience here now.
May need more coal.
I feel like I should have more, but I don't.
Okay, well, let's go find those cows.
Also, I don't know where my, uh, contraption is, my digging machine.
Tell me we have cows somewhere.
Maybe this way.
Did I see one?
No, I mean, that's a different kind of cow.
That's a little bastard.
I don't need no stinking shield.
I've got armor.
If you think about it, armor is just a shield, but shaped to your body.
Are you stuck in there?
That sucks.
Ominous bottle?
We can use that in the trial chamber.
Show me the cows.
I killed them all, didn't I?
I do have memories of walking around here just killing everything.
Am I so blood hungry?
Classic fault of mine, you know?
There's a pig.
I guess we can take some pigs.
Do they like wheat?
You like this?
They don't.
Okay, they probably want seeds.
I actually don't know what pigs eat, man.
Another pig over there.
Black sheep.
Come on, cows!
We just need two.
Oh, there's one.
I wonder, though, if we should mix the cows and the sheep.
Yeah, why not?
They're gonna get along, right?
I'll even take this cow over here.
Come with me.
Don't mind me eating this.
It's not cow meat.
It's sheep.
Come on.
And I...
Dude, we can also milk these cows.
And then we can use the milk.
And we can transport the milk via pipes.
Straight into my mouth.
I actually don't even like milk in real life.
Like, just drinking it, you know?
I use it in cooking and stuff, but just drinking it, man?
That's weird.
Oh, we even got a stray sheep here.
That's cool.
Everyone is welcome!
Let's go!
God, it's so slow, though.
Come on.
Follow me to get to your sanitary new home.
Humane home.
Oh, I see the enclosure!
Are you guys excited?
I wonder how far I can take this.
If I just run.
No, okay.
He's very confused now.
I'm honestly not even sure if it's faster with lead.
Because sometimes they would get stuck with the lead, and you'd have to pick up the lead again, and, you know, that has its own little set of problems.
Come on.
It's like they need a moment to react when I switch items.
There we go!
What's up, everybody?
Make sure to feed the cows first.
And then we feed some sheep.
Yeah.
Everyone's so happy.
Okay, let's go close this.
A proper farm is being made here!
Feels so good, man.
Let's go grab more wheat.
I mean, okay, it's not the fastest, you know, but we definitely need more wheat down the line.
Um, right.
I was- oh, that's what I was doing.
I was looking for the disenchanting thing.
Let me just take a look through everything.
I'm gonna start from the other end.
Just for fun.
Isn't that fun?
I think it's fun.
Can't stop laughing.
Dropper.
Spencer.
I'll know it when I see it.
Basically.
Assuming I have the recipe for it.
Analog transmission.
Kinda wanna make that.
What's that?
Cardboard chess plate.
Did I ever try to make that?
Wasn't that something about- Yeah, stealth.
Yo, we should try to do that, actually.
But we gotta make pulp for that.
So we gotta set up the whole, you know, squishing machine setup.
Don't have that right now.
It's this one!
It's the grindstone!
But don't I have that?
No, I don't!
Oh my god!
Stone slabs, sticks, and planks.
Uh, planks, uh, stone, slab.
Oh, hell yeah.
This is the one!
How did I fuck this up so much lately?
Like, I couldn't even...
Yeah!
Finally!
I have done it!
Burn that.
What else can I disenchant?
Let's take this one.
And that one...
Uh...
I must have something else.
This one.
And that one.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it's not a lot of experience, but you know, it's something.
Right, that one doesn't work for some reason.
Okay.
I'm guessing it's because of the curse of vanishing.
Nice.
Just another thing checked off the list here.
Wonderful.
Okay, man.
This is good!
We got the farm done.
We got disenchanter now.
Oh, it's beautiful.
We're getting back on our feet.
Last time...
Man, I really had a whole episode last time, didn't I?
It was not pretty.
I lost almost everything.
But it's okay.
Things are looking up again.
It's not much, but it's honest work right here, you know?
You're not ready to be fed yet, huh?
Come on, you must be ready.
One of them was ready just now.
Come on, one more cow.
No?
I fed the little one.
Okay, whatever.
Enjoy!
Let's go to bed.
Ah, feels good so far.
Reminds me of that farm I had in the first season.
In that valley, you know?
I really love that farm, actually.
I miss that.
We're gonna do that again.
Different animals.
We're gonna have chickens, too.
Chickens...
Need chicken feed.
Ooh, I have a lot of this.
So that should be super easy.
This one is still cooking.
No, it's not.
Ran out of materials.
Uh, damn.
Kinda running low on coal here.
Dude, where is my digging machine?
Because that one, I think, has coal.
Oh, wait, it blew up!
A creeper blew it up, remember?
It's not here.
It's gone.
Right!
I remember that now.
Frick.
Maybe my plan of having obsidian all around it is a good idea, then.
You know, like, some kind of blast insulation.
Hmm.
I do have 16 drills, though.
I mean, it's not...
I can easily get back to where I was.
Not a big deal.
Leave this here.
Yeah.
It's not that bad.
It's also these ones.
How about we start with this, actually?
I've been wanting to do this for a while.
What would I want to automatically craft?
What is something...
Let me see this one.
Oh, yeah, right.
You can bring in items with this.
This seems like a whole thing, doesn't it?
Wait a second.
Isn't this just a better way of doing a lot of the automated stuff that I'm doing in the factory over here right now?
You know, I guess some things can only be done by, you know, using a press or whatever, but some things can just be combined in the normal inventory.
And it's much more versatile, in a way.
Let me see here.
What was it?
Mechanical crafter.
Yeah, look at this.
Like, there's all kinds of things you can make that are, like, way bigger than a normal crafting setup.
Mounted potato cannon.
I mean...
What even is that, you know?
Should we try and make that?
Docking connector.
This is something I'm less excited about.
Because I think it's just gonna...
Isn't it just gonna connect two things together?
Doesn't sound too wild.
This one sounds interesting.
Crushing wheel.
Doesn't really sound that interesting.
I think I'm gonna try and make this.
So I need eight of these.
Oops, what did I just do?
Oh, never mind.
I have three.
Me- Mechanical crafter.
The tubes, huh?
Do I have any?
Oh, I actually have some.
Hey, we can potentially do this.
Brass casing and crafting table.
Okay, that's not even that hard.
Brass casing.
I've got it!
Construction, I've got this one too.
And in terms of wood, we can just make more.
Wait, how is it?
Oh wait, it's four.
Ah, there it is.
Let's just make a couple.
Like that.
We got nine.
One more than we need.
Perfect.
So let me see the thing.
Dude, you need 21 for this one.
Like, that's freaking crazy.
Copper sh...
Okay, so I guess we need to make it in this shape, right?
Okay, this is actually kind of exciting.
Uh, okay.
So we make it in that shape.
Right.
Let me try it outside.
Oh, let's do it!
Dude, let's do it over here.
Oh, I was gonna do it along this wall, but there's not actually room right now.
It would be perfect, wouldn't it?
I guess I could relocate this.
I do have silk touch.
Yeah, it's no big deal.
Ah, but wait a second!
Uh, ponder that again.
Doesn't it need...
Yeah, it needs, like, rotation.
From the side.
Okay, okay, okay.
Got it.
Let me just try to do this.
So it's like this.
Oops.
Oh, no.
Gimme.
Right.
Wait, how does this work again?
I need to...
One more time.
An array of mechanical crafters can be used to automate any crafting recipe.
Yep.
Using a wrench, the crafter's paths can be arranged.
Yeah.
For a valid setup, all paths have to converge into one exit at any side.
Okay, so isn't it just, um...
Down, down, right,
right, down, and then we put a chest or something?
We put this at the end.
And then we're gonna crank that shit!
One wheel.
And...
Do I even have a crank?
I may have lost it in the great disaster of 26.
I guess we should make one anyway.
I mean, if I'm gonna go chop wood at some point, right, I'm gonna need this.
Alloy and...
Okay, that's easy.
So we should just do like this.
Once again, every orientation except the one I want.
Like, this game just is trolling me.
Like, it's crazy.
It's like it's designed to be rage bait.
There we go.
Wait, what?
What happened?
Automated assembly.
I didn't even do anything.
Which one is it?
Oh!
Dude, maybe I should actually start looking at this more and do this in like...
the proper order.
I still haven't done a windmill of maximum strain.
Like, how many do I need?
What the hell, man?
Compactification.
Use a mechanical press and a basin to operate fewer or create fewer items from more.
I feel like I've done that, though.
Witness your cuckoo clock announce bedtime.
Lower a hose pulley and watch it drain or fill a body of fluid.
Wait!
You can do that?
How does that even make sense?
Operate a pair of crushing wheels at maximum strength.
Yeah, but for that I need like a million of these.
Obtain some train tracks.
Assemble a steam whistle to your train and activate it while driving.
Assemble a sturdy sheet by refining powdered obsidian.
Dude, maybe this is what I need for the train.
Maybe the steam whistle is like the thing that unlocks something else.
So I guess it's all connected here.
I need to make these.
And get a sturdy sheet.
Watch your mechanical arm transport its first item.
I wish I could make this.
Engineers hate this simple trick.
Fine-tune your contraption with a rotation speed controller.
Hmm.
I guess for that you need this.
Assemble a precision mechanism.
I haven't done that yet.
Okay, well, let me try this first.
So, now that we have this.
Okay, so we need copper sheet.
Okay, that's very specific.
Copper sheet, dried kelp block.
Do I even have that?
I actually have it!
That's amazing.
Then we needed the copper sheets.
Cog wheel, fluid pipes, and dust.
Okay.
Fluid pipes.
I must have some of those.
I guess I'll make them.
Needs a normal one, too.
Guess we have those here!
What's the difference?
Oh, you can make them different ways.
Uh, what else did I need?
The cog wheel, right.
Don't I have that?
Okay, so here we go.
Are you ready?
Here, here.
I will remember this configuration.
Yes, and...
Oh, uh, this one here.
Oh, shit, shit.
I fucked it up, I fucked it up.
This one here.
And then...
Oh god, I already forgot.
I need to remember this.
Oh, redstone dust!
Here, here.
And...
What else did I need?
Oh, these ones!
There, there.
And I...
Oh, I pipe at the end.
You ready?
Let's try it.
It appears that this contraption is overstressed.
Add more sources or slow down the components.
Really?
Hand cranking is too fast?
Guess I don't know my own strength.
That's wild.
Guess I'll need some bigger wheels.
Let's put these in the garden as well.
And put them here.
One there.
And maybe this guy.
Wonderful.
Now, big wheel time.
And maybe some shafts.
Also, this banner is pissing me off.
Get it out of my sight.
Also, uh, quick detour!
We're gonna go feed the animals.
We gotta keep the feeding up.
Create a big strong herd.
There you go, buddy.
Look how many there is already.
It's fantastic.
Make kits!
There you go.
In no time, we're gonna have so much food.
And the best part is, it's so simple.
And for the longest time, I've just been a dumbass about it, you know?
No more!
Those days are over.
Only intelligent decisions from now on.
No more misplays.
Only good stuff.
You'll see.
Okay, so what we want to do now, we want to slow down this.
So I guess, just naively, let's, uh...
It's gonna be a little ugly.
You know?
Well, maybe that's okay.
Put a small wheel here.
And then we're gonna have a big wheel, uh, there.
And I guess we can maybe try now.
What?!
Overstressed!
Really?
Okay, well, let's try again then.
Like here, and then another big wheel.
Not down there, that's ugly.
I guess this is fine.
This is the ugliest thing I've ever done, but okay.
Wait, hold on.
Add more sources, or slow down the components.
Wait, what do you mean overstressed?
It means there's too much power, right?
I mean, let's just try and clip through the stuff here.
It's fine for now.
If I rotate this...
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I did the opposite thing.
Look at him go!
Oh my god, it's moving!
Crack that shit!
Workout session!
That's right.
I'm taking damage?
Wait, what?
Oh my god, it's draining my...
Look at that!
And...
It's the...
Wait, why am I dying?
Oh, shit!
I...
Oh, oh!
I see, I see, I see, I see.
I fucking eat something.
No!
Jesus Christ!
I'm feeling bloated already from all these berries.
Okay, so I obviously fucked up out here because I can't open the chest.
Mounted potato cannon!
Ponder on that.
Let's see.
It's a block version of the potato cannon.
Wait.
I didn't even know there was a potato cannon.
It accepts the same ammo...
Okay, so a potato, I guess.
And can be loaded by automated means.
Wait, did I just miss something here?
Po-ta-to!
Boil him, mash him, stick him in a stew.
I don't have access to that.
Not right now, at least.
All right, well...
So we now...
We know how this works now, and we can connect it to a power source, I guess.
Next up, we want to make more crafters.
Because I think we can make trains that way.
What does it take to make crafter again?
Oh, it's electron tube, isn't it?
Tube.
Sheet and polished rose quartz.
Polished rose quartz.
Wait, polished rose quartz.
Isn't that just this and redstone dust?
And then we need to rub it, you know?
Where is it?
My rubbing mechanism.
There we go.
So, rose...
Oh, it's quartz!
Right.
I thought it was this one.
Okay.
Actually, you know, electron tubes, they're not even that hard to make.
Iron sheet...
Oh, that's probably the...
Yeah.
That's the bottleneck right now.
We don't even have any means of making that.
Shit.
That's right, last time I had big problems finding iron.
May have to go find a couple more irons, you know?
And we're not gonna cry like a little bitch about it.
We're just gonna go do it this time.
No more whining.
Just get to work, man.
Put this here.
We're gonna clean the inventory properly.
I guess we can put this in here for now.
Shafts.
And ominous bottle.
That's a miscellaneous...
I'm happy.
Put that on.
So, uh...
Didn't we get some diamonds?
Two of them.
That is not good enough.
I'm gonna burn some wood.
Yeah, that's all the diamond I have.
We may have to go find some, uh...
Uh...
Iron and diamond.
And we're just gonna do it and not bitch about it.
That's the plan right now.
Also fill this up fully.
With, uh, all the stuff that we have.
I'm gonna bring these two diamonds with me so I can make a pickaxe in the field when it's time.
Clipboard.
Let's update that real quick.
This one is...
We're not doing that anymore.
We're done with that.
Uh, collection method.
Boo.
This one is pretty relevant.
We're gonna keep that.
This one's relevant and, um...
Don't, uh...
This is the motto for today.
Don't be a bitch.
Don't do it.
Just do it, man.
We got the silk touch.
We got the axe.
Shovel.
Anything else?
We got bow, arrows, infinity.
Yes.
Food.
Let's go feed some cows.
You know what, actually?
I'm gonna go to a village.
And I'm gonna rob them.
Only cows get fed.
There you go.
Uh, I am gonna leave you guys alive for now because we're not done feeding.
I will get my food elsewhere.
I'm gonna rob a village of a bunch of food.
This is my short-term plan of getting food.
Boat.
I need a bed.
Uh, do I need a bed, though?
Yes.
I need a bed.
No way around it.
Bedtime.
There you go.
I'll even grab this and turn them into that.
So I have it.
Yes, sir.
What is in this?
Aha!
Well, there you go.
Why don't you look at that?
Some random stuff.
I'm happy.
Let's go.
Uh, maybe I'll bring some shitty food just, uh, temporarily here.
I'll eat a cookie.
Sugar rush before the expedition.
And some berries.
I know where there's a village nearby.
We're gonna go to that.
Let's lock up before we leave.
And go to bed.
Honey, I'm off!
Look at all these zombies burning.
Feels good, yo.
I wish there was a way to sort of purify or fix or, you know, healthify the cancerous meat.
And turn it into the good meat.
You know how you can haunt things?
I want to do the opposite of that.
The village should be on the other side of this mountain, I think.
Or maybe up here-ish.
Wait, there's actually pumpkin.
But I can't really just eat that.
But you can make pumpkin pie, right?
Isn't that a thing?
Wait, is that even good?
I forgot how good that is for my food.
Because if it's really good, we may create a pumpkin factory.
Pumpkin pie factory.
PPF.
Sounds like something I would love to do.
You don't want to eat meat every day, you know?
You gotta have some days without meat.
So we're not gonna forget where we are.
And the good part about this, I'm also going in a direction that is a little different than usual.
So when we find a cave, it's gonna be a fresh one.
Hey, cow.
I could actually kill you.
I'm gonna do it.
Why is there not a village here?
I feel like there was a village here.
My memory fails me.
Dude, this is actually such a picturesque area.
Look at this river!
Wouldn't be too bad to have like a summer house up here on the cliff, you know?
Full glass room, looking out.
Not too shabby.
Okay, this village is nowhere to be seen.
Okay, it should be on the other side here.
There it is.
We got it, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm not gonna walk in these, because it hurts.
Get out of my sight.
There's also a crazy cave there.
We could actually go there after.
Dude, it's kind of wild that there's no sounds when you do stuff like that, you know?
Why is there not like at least a little bonk sound when you hit the floor with that?
For a game that has such a big studio behind it right now, you know?
It does feel weirdly incomplete, almost?
Okay, so the goal is to find a bunch of wheat.
And steal it.
Okay, so they have pumpkins.
But do they have wheat?
Usually these villages have wheat.
Unless it is like a thing where some villages in certain biomes have pumpkins instead of wheat.
It's like their main source of nutrition.
Dude, I'm kind of thinking that's the case here.
Which sucks ass!
I don't like that.
Can I survive on berries though?
That's the question.
Little foxes.
Okay, let's see if they have some actual food.
Maybe in chests or something.
This is the most scuffed way of getting food.
We got some!
I feel like a little homeless kid in the 1800s, you know, on the street trying to steal an apple.
Pumpkin pie!
Hey, that makes so much sense.
All things considered here.
With their local produce.
I'll take this too.
Wait, that's new?
Sprues!
Wow!
Can't believe I haven't found that yet.
Actually, I'll take this bell.
Thanks.
Nah, you can have it.
Don't want that.
Kids jumping on the bed.
Classic.
Okay, not bad.
Potatoes.
I guess we can make baked potatoes.
Not really feeling that.
Damn.
Well, it is what it is.
So the pumpkin pie just gave me four food.
Pumpkin pie is just as good as meat, it seems.
It may be on the level of steak.
Okay, let's head into a cave.
And let's not forget, I have gone west so far, so the way to get home is east.
Oh, I see iron already.
The problem is, I have a silk touch pickaxe, but it's actually not a problem.
We can make a stone pickaxe, or even an iron pickaxe, very soon.
Yeah, let's do that.
Ah, but to do that, I need a stone pickaxe first.
It sounds really dumb, but I do.
Make some of this.
Wait, what?
Why can't I make stone?
It needs to be cobblestone!
I can't even grab that.
That's wild.
What about andesite?
Brother, man.
Okay, there's a way we can do this.
I actually started hating silk touch.
I'm not even... like, this silk touch sucks!
I'm on team anti-silk touch.
Okay, now, stone pickaxe.
Finally.
And with the stone pickaxe, we can get an iron pickaxe.
We're going through all the different materials here.
Did I just throw away the wrong one?
God damn it!
Here we go.
Grab some of this.
That way we can actually cook the iron we find, so we can make an iron pickaxe.
In a world of create like this, I'm out here mining with a goddamn stone pickaxe.
You know how humiliating that is?
Burn!
Nice.
I see that up there.
That right there is my pickaxe.
Got it.
Now to make a furnace.
I'm gonna grab this.
Cobblestone.
I forgot how many I need.
Like, eight or something?
Iron.
And then we can make a pickaxe.
And then we are rolling.
In case I need to make a couple torches or something.
There we go.
It's time.
We got it.
The means to mine.
And let's go into the mine.
Things are looking up.
Uh, oh shit.
I can't think.
Brett.
That's the one I need.
Playing it so safe right now.
Man, their shooting cadence is so high.
More iron.
Dude, this is the perfect cave so far.
For what I need.
Also, someone did point out that apparently the creative tracks aren't really playing.
So I need to confirm that I've actually activated this mod that I installed.
I may have fucked it up.
Either that or I'm just very unlucky.
Because I do want to hear those tracks, you know?
More iron?
I love this cave.
Oh!
Uh, diamonds is also something we need.
But we gotta go a little deeper for that.
I just want to get my share of iron first.
Look at all these enemies here!
This is like a whole fucking harem.
The gang hideout has been located.
Actually, I have a bow.
I think.
Where's my bow?
I can't!
I want the time pressure!
There it is.
Is the bow even better?
It feels shit.
What's with these spiders?
Why are they drunk?
Fuck!
Oh no!
I may be in trouble!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Being stuck in a hole like that?
No good.
Good thing I have my armor.
Okay, okay.
Everything's fine.
I don't want this disgusting coal ore!
Ew!
Get this out of my face!
Actually, a string is something I do need a little bit of, but...
I don't want to go down there and pick it up.
I'll take this instead.
Only four loaves of bread left.
I do wish I had Lempa's bread right now.
Nothing exciting over there.
No iron for moi?
Um, I don't think I need zinc.
Not currently.
Give me more coal.
There we go!
And we gotta go deeper anyway.
Should I just do it?
Attack!
Too bad I didn't have the hammer, huh?
Could have done some damage.
Oh, look at this massive deposit of iron here.
There's even more!
Huge!
This cave is so much better than the other cave I have at home.
So far, at least.
Could be diamonds down there.
Man, iron pickaxes are really good.
Like, they're solid, you know?
They last a long time.
It's not too slow.
It's not super fast, of course, but...
But what it is, it's really good.
Iron pickaxes deserve your respect.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm going down.
Oh!
Massive iron!
I see it, but I also see danger.
How do I approach this?
What's up, brother?
Cute!
Explode then, I don't care.
Don't like all those creepers.
They could end me right now.
Yeah, okay, why not?
Oi!
That was a whole pool.
Now that's what I'm talking about!
Look at all those goodies!
My ankles.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, there's more!
We're gonna make a diamond pickaxe right now.
Maybe down here.
Make sure no enemies are spawning.
I want to be left in peace.
We're still back.
Get rid of this crap.
I will never touch iron again.
It sucks.
I think I also need more of this.
I'm running low on redstone.
I'll take some gold, too.
This is a fucking Schlaraffenland!
And I'm all here for it.
Now, there was one time when I was down here, and I was having a good time, and then all of a sudden I just got blown up.
No warning, no nothing.
A creeper from the freaking air just fell down on me and exploded on me.
So let's keep in mind that something like that could happen.
I'm gonna be extra careful.
More redstone.
Don't mind if I do.
Now, what else do I need?
Do I even need more diamonds?
I actually forgot why I came here.
It was just mainly iron, right?
I needed iron so I could make pressed iron.
Right, that's why.
And then I wanted to get diamonds anyway, since I was going mining.
And maybe we can even enchant a pickaxe today, if we get to 30.
You look so silly with no shirt on.
So far, this place has been magnificent.
That's my last bread.
But I do have a furnace, and I can cook this meat, so I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna play this so safe.
And good thing we have lava over here.
That means easy deletion.
I'll keep the leather.
The rest is whatever.
Where are my sticks?
I mean, my... oh, my coal is here, of course.
I'll make a couple more torches.
64.
And then we have some meat now.
Things are looking up.
I just unlocked something.
Painting.
What's up, guys?
How's it hanging?
Go even deeper.
Should I, though?
Ow.
I smell diamonds.
I'm trying not to panic.
I'm just...
I'm just handling it.
I actually keep thinking of, um...
Oh, wait.
There's my thing.
Okay.
Why did it sound like my shield was breaking just now?
Did you hear that sound?
I keep thinking of ADHD, you know?
Like, if I actually have it, what it would feel like to get the medicine, you know?
Like, I keep thinking of the movie Limitless, because someone once told me that it's like taking the pill from Limitless, you know?
And that sounds fucking crazy to me.
Like, I...
Part of me kind of wants to have ADHD and then have the pill taken and then have that feeling.
Obviously, it's probably best if I don't have it, so I don't know.
What is even happening here?
Dude, I'm playing this masterfully?
There we go.
It was masterful until I said masterfully and then it became not masterfully.
Oh my god, bro!
Get away from me.
You also have an Enderman here.
I will kill him.
Come at me!
I've got NADP.
Sounds like some kind of disease.
Okay, next time we go mining, I will bring bottles of vision.
A vision enhancer.
Potion of foresight, whatever, you know what I mean.
See in the dark.
Gimme.
Okay, now check it out.
I am too damn greedy, know when to stop.
I know when to stop.
And it's right now.
We're stopping now.
Because I only have one piece of food left.
We got what we came for.
We're good.
I'm a changed man.
Never mind, there's more.
I mean, if they come at me like that, I take them, you know.
Let's go up.
Here we go!
Guys, it's going to be day, because today is a good day.
And it's not a good day if it's night.
You know why?
Because it'd be a good night instead.
My logic is flawless!
How much iron did I bring?
38.
Okay, that's something.
It's not amazing, but it's all right.
Maybe we can even find a couple more on the way out of here.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Oh, shit, I ran out of up!
Oh, I ran out of up!
Bro, are you?
Not in a hole again!
I hate myself.
For getting into situations like this constantly.
I guess we're doing berries now.
I do love me some berry.
And no-ho-hank.
One of the best characters ever, actually.
Ever on TV.
It's gotta be no-ho-hank.
Uh, give me this.
Actually huge that we find this iron on the way up.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna mine this, obviously, since it's here.
You can't tell me not to mine it.
If you offer me cake, I eat it, you know?
Just double-checking, we don't have any...
Okay, okay, okay, fine.
I'm outta here.
I'm going up here.
It's still gonna be day outside.
I know it.
I have foreseen it.
Are you ready for day?
If it's day, uh...
Then...
Guys, if it's day outside, then all our dreams will collectively come true.
Yours and mine.
Okay?
The thing that's on your mind right now, the thing you're worried about in life...
That one thing, you know what it is.
That worry will just go away if it's day.
If it's night, however, that one thing on your mind is gonna get worse.
And it's gonna suck for all of us, collectively.
So, you better predict day.
There's something I have in mind.
It's something I ate.
It better be day.
I hear animals.
Ah!
Congratulations, everybody!
All our problems are solved!
It's a new era.
That feels incredible.
Everything's gonna be alright.
Uh, that's west.
So we go this way.
I will murder cows on the way, too.
Get rid of all this crap.
Let's go home, shall we?
And I followed the rule.
The rule of not be greedy.
Thank you.
Kind of want to bring home a couple chickens as well.
But I think this guy's a little too far away.
I don't want to be pulling him all the way from here.
It's gonna take ages to get home.
Uh, this is the mountain that I was on.
And I saw a village, I believe?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the cave.
That's beautiful.
I know exactly where I am.
I can even go boating.
With Adrian.
I've missed you, Adrian.
We're gonna go on the high seas together.
And explore the world.
Brody quest.
So, I'm actually real.
I'm gonna make the pumpkin pie factory.
At some point.
Because, um...
Yes, it's good to have, like, cows that produce meat.
But think of it like this.
If we have multiple sources of food income...
We will never go hungry again.
Not only that.
We will never go hungry for...
Change in our diet, either.
We're gonna have a varied diet.
And we're gonna be super healthy.
We're gonna eat bread.
Pumpkin pie.
And steaks.
Mutton chops or pork chops.
Berries.
And chocolate cookies for dessert.
I'm making myself so hungry right now.
What's up, piggy?
Wait, no.
Pork chops are from pigs.
And mutton chops are from meep.
Cheap.
That's how...
That's how you should remember that.
And we made it.
Fantastic.
Let's cook some iron, boys.
Uh...
Hold on.
I prioritize.
Iron.
Go.
Cook it for me.
While that's cooking...
What am I gonna do?
Fix my inventory, I guess.
Silk touch.
Yeah, you're done.
No more silk touch.
Get out of here.
We also have all this diamond now.
Hmm.
Feel like I should make...
Some basic stuff here, like a shovel and another axe.
Yeah.
Why not?
Gotta get the basics down, right?
Uh, for that we need some sticks.
Asks.
This one does have efficiency on it.
So maybe we just repair it.
Eh?
Not a bad idea.
Hell yeah.
And then a shovel.
I'm gonna burn this in righteous fire.
Oh, I also had string.
I forgot why I needed string.
I needed string for something at some point.
But I forget-y.
Got more redstone.
That's actually kind of huge.
Really needed that.
Now I need to make the press so we can make these, uh...
Pressed iron thingies.
Right, we don't have that anymore out here.
But I guess we can, you know, quickly take the rotation from here.
And use it to our advantage.
Just real quick, you know?
Just a quickie.
So we need a bench press, or whatever it's called.
Uh, the little slab that you slap, uh...
The thing on.
The depot.
And of course, the press itself.
Where did I hide you?
What do you look like?
What is your name?
Did I get red- Oh, wait.
I probably used it in the factory?
Or what?
Maybe I might make a new one?
Oh, block of iron?
I don't have that.
Okay, we're gonna go, uh...
Cannibalize.
I am running low on iron right now.
I need all the iron I can get.
I mean, this thing over here has, like, a bunch.
There's, like, three in a row here.
No, there's one.
Uh, I'll take it.
Thank you.
I do want to make a path that connects the factory, too.
Man, I can't even sprint.
Cheers, guys.
Happy Sunday.
I hope you're feeling mega relaxed.
And that you're at peace in your mind.
Now, especially, that we know all your wishes will come true after we saw that it was day when I predicted it.
That should put a smile on your face.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Uh, we got some raw gold, too.
Don't want that.
Uno torcho.
Okay, how we doing here?
Twenty...
Forty-five so far.
Nice.
Um...
And we have what it takes now.
Let's grab some of that food.
Oh, I don't even have any, like, food.
Cook the beef.
Eat it.
Yeah, it gives four.
Just like the pumpkin pie.
I'll take one more.
There you go.
Oh, let's feed the animals?
Before we forget?
Obviously, we're not quite duplicating every time, you know, powers of whatever.
It's not happening with this little amount of food.
But, you know, it's something.
Fine, you can make babies, too.
Go.
I think they love their new enclosure, guys.
I feel so much better about it.
What's in here?
Take that.
My shield is about to break.
You know what that means?
That means I break it first.
Let's deploy it!
It's press time!
Oh, it's already beautifully deployed.
And now we should just be able to do this.
Press it for me.
But we don't want it to press everything.
Maybe half.
There you go.
And why am I...
Wait, why am I even doing this?
I forgot what the purpose was.
Uh, I was making...
Tubes.
But why was I making tubes?
Oh yeah, the crafters.
That's why.
Oh yeah, right.
I had the polished quartz here.
Uh, well, not yet.
Almost.
Wait, am I eating that?
No, okay.
I thought I had to have it in the other hand.
It looked like he was eating it.
Oh, I broke the sandpaper.
Uh, I guess I need sand and paper, right?
That was the rule!
Pape...
I don't have paper.
But I have cardboard.
Can I use that to make paper?
Shit!
Maybe it was here.
Sandpaper...
Shit!
Balls!
Okay, we don't need to make them all anyway.
It's okay.
Let's go grab these plates.
And set the table.
Yoink!
Electron tubes for everyone.
Six of them!
Nice!
And...
Crafter...
Mechanical crafter.
Needed crafting tables and brass casings.
And I think I actually...
I have some.
Nice.
May need more.
Brass casing.
Brass...
Wait, what?
Oh, wait.
Wasn't it just, uh...
Oaks?
Like that.
And then we brass it up.
Wonderful.
Make a couple more.
Six.
And crafting tables.
That one's easy.
That's just a bunch of planks.
Ten.
27 mechanical crafters!
I think that's way more than I need.
Let me see here.
I need 21 to do this.
To make that one.
And I do want to make that one.
Let's do it!
Let's just do it!
We're going to need a lot of space for this one.
What would a good spot be?
Maybe out here?
Somewhere?
I want it to be looking nice as well, kind of.
You know what I mean?
Yo, let's do it!
Wait, I wonder if I can do them...
Uh...
Vertically.
Like this.
Ah, probably not.
Yeah.
Too bad.
Wait, 21.
Wait, hold on.
That's like a...
That's a lot.
5 in height.
Okay, that's kind of crazy.
I mean, I could just make them somewhere random.
But I kind of don't want to do that.
This wall is made for it, isn't it?
I like this wall.
1, 2, 3, 4...
Nah, there's no room on that wall.
Unfortunately.
Fuck it, let's do it outside.
Uh...
There we go.
And then...
What was it?
3.
Oh, okay.
That makes more sense.
That's crazy.
I'm gonna remove this.
Okay, so I guess we wanna...
Result in an output.
Somewhere here.
So I'm just gonna do that.
I'm gonna put a little chesty.
So we can testy.
And this is going that way.
I guess we want all of it to go that way at the end.
So that goes in there.
I guess these will have to go up.
Like that.
Wait.
Down.
Left.
Right.
They all collect here.
Fall down here.
They're all gonna go there.
And then that should work.
I think.
Then we need...
Oh my god!
We need a lot of andesite alloy!
I don't have that, I don't think.
And then we need planks and diorite.
Sure.
Why not?
Plank me.
I'll use birch.
Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb.
And diorite.
Oh, I guess andesite also worked.
Ba-dum.
14?
Is that enough?
One, two, three.
And it's all...
Oh my god!
It's exactly what I need!
That's wild.
Never mind, it's not.
I can't count.
Uh...
Alloy.
Andesite and nuggets.
Right.
Nugget me!
There we go.
Wrong one.
Okay, and then we need it...
That's...
So wait.
They go down.
That way.
Oh wait, this one needs to...
Point down.
Okay.
I think it looks good.
Now we need some power.
And I've got it.
I've got it all here.
And my crank as well.
We're gonna crank the shit out of this.
Let's make it...
There.
You ready?
Here we go!
Ah!
Okay, fine.
Wait, wait.
How's that...
How's that gonna work?
They're connected...
Wait, what?
Does that even make sense?
Wait, I'm simply curious at this point.
Okay, yeah.
That breaks that.
Interesting.
I was like, that shouldn't work at all!
Why was I able to place it in the first place?
You know?
Wait, what's wrong?
Oh, wait.
I want to do the opposite.
I'm going the wrong way here.
We want to go from small to big.
So, you know what?
Why don't we just put a big one here?
Ah, well, we can't.
Small to big.
And right now, it's not enough, right?
Yeah.
Give me a big one.
But this should work.
Why isn't this working?
This should be mega slow.
It's overstressed.
Add more sources or slow down the components.
I guess it...
Maybe because it's bigger?
It needs to be even more slow?
I guess so.
Wait, desperate measures?
Let's see.
Look, they're moving!
They're moving so slow.
And then they meet up there.
They're going to go down into that.
And then they're going to go...
Yeah, I think the configuration is correct, though.
What if I stop, Mint?
Oh!
Right, it's hard work.
Dude!
It literally looks like a wheel!
I didn't even think about that!
That makes so much sense!
And...
Yes!
We move them all over there to that...
Look how slow it is!
Oh my god!
I can't do this for much longer!
I can't do it!
Is it being made?
Why is it...
What's happening?
And...
Oh, it's becoming smaller again!
It's gone!
Crushing wheel!
Ooh!
Ooh, wait, what is that?
Let's see.
A pair of crushing wheels can grind items very effectively.
Wait.
Are you saying...
Orphan grinder?
Perhaps?
A rotational input has to make them spin into each other.
Okay.
Got it.
That makes sense, I guess.
Items thrown or inserted into the top will get processed.
Okay.
What's the difference between this and...
a mill?
Items can be inserted and picked up through automated means as well.
Right.
Makes sense.
Why even need a funnel here?
Can't you just let it fall down or what?
Maybe because of filter?
Okay.
I mean, okay.
So they can...
crush things?
Huh.
Alright.
Let me see the achievements.
Operate a pair of crushing wheels at maximum speed.
But wait, why is this one in front of this stuff?
Oh, maybe you need this to make this?
Cause potato cannon projectiles of different types to collide with each other.
And then create a minecart contraption that places tracks in front of itself.
I did that one already.
It's also...
Okay, it's also here.
Place in power instead of crushing wheels.
Oh, this is at maximum speed.
Oh, okay.
Let me see...
Oh, yeah.
Aserene.
Oh, wait.
I get sink out of that.
What the hell?
Okay.
I get iron out of Cribsite!
Wait, crushed raw iron?
What is that?
Crushed raw iron?
What does that even mean?
40% chance.
Diorite becomes nether quartz?
Tough becomes whatever?
Wait, what the fuck?
Nugget of experience?
A speck of inspiration from your fantastic inventions.
Redeems experience points contained within...
Wait, what the hell?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Andesite into cobblestone.
Wait a minute.
Wait, this is like way more efficient.
You get like two, potentially three.
Instead of one.
Oh, my God.
Dude, this thing is insane.
Coal or look at this.
Wait.
Potentially two coal?
Silk touch is my best friend again.
I was on the hate train for silk touch.
Okay, so you definitely want them in this format then.
Potentially three diamonds and experience.
That, okay.
Dripstone block becomes clay.
Endstone becomes endstone powder.
Ooh, I want to do that.
Oh, this is nice.
Dude, this is like a game changer.
Iron ore.
Dude, what is crushed raw iron?
I want to make that.
I need to see.
Okay.
Oh, sick.
We could even make that.
Cinderflower.
From netherrack.
Okay.
Obsidian.
Powered obsidian.
Peony.
Okay.
This, I'm so curious about.
Like, the crushed versions.
Guys, you know what this is?
This is basically a machine.
Ho- Guys.
I- This is actually...
All I ever wanted.
This is the dream for me.
You know why?
Because I come home.
What do I do?
I just empty all my shit into the crushing!
I fix my inventory.
And I get extra items out of it.
Well, obviously I don't want to throw everything in there.
But, you know, all this stuff, obviously, we want to throw in there.
Wheat becomes wheat flour!
Bro.
We are doing that right now.
I can't wait!
Uh, maybe I'll leave this for now.
Where do we put these wheels?
Maybe somewhere out here.
No.
Inside.
Uh.
Oh my god.
Um.
Someone's texting me.
I need to...
What?
Okay, hold on.
Where's the lever here for...
Look how fast that is!
Maybe the crushing wheels are down there!
Incredible elevator!
Yes!
Let's go!
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's make them here!
Let's see.
Not that way!
Ah, wait a second.
Actually, take me back up!
I guess I gotta climb it.
This is the one downside to my mechanism here.
Ah, there we go.
Bring it back up!
Oh, I don't like this part!
The floating part needs to be fixed.
That's no bueno.
We gotta...
Use some of that glue on it.
That should work.
Let's see.
Yay!
Look at the cookies go!
Cookies on an elevator!
This is...
Song title.
Of my future albums.
Ah...
Oh my god, oh my god.
Let's...
Let's put these...
Bro, I don't know where to put them!
I guess somewhere where we have rotation...
Anyway.
Like, we have a lot of rotation here.
Look at all this rotation right there.
Like, that's wasted.
Right?
We gotta use that somehow.
Hmm.
Maybe we bring that rotation outside.
So it's gonna come through the wall.
Like this.
That way.
Gonna go...
Oh, that actually looks kinda nice too.
I dig that!
Yes, let's do it.
That's a good plan.
First though, we clean up the inventory because it's looking like crap right now.
No surprise.
Always like that.
Ah, this is redstone, I would say.
That's, uh...
Green.
Ingots are in here.
Oh god.
We gotta make, like, an item, uh...
Sorter.
Soonish.
Like, a really good one that...
Takes advantage of create.
You know?
Because I'm losing my mind.
It's the silly song again?
I never see it coming.
Like, I heard the first part of the song, and I was like...
That's not it.
Turns out it is.
Why do I have two clipboards?
Don't be a bitch!
That's what it says.
Words to live by.
Put them on the...
Wall?
Change...
Oh!
This is my to-do list.
Let me put that back over here.
Let's put the boat in there.
And we also...
Oh, and the side casing is something I need now.
So I need...
Shafts.
And I need wheels.
Basically the stuff I just put away.
Hey!
Oi!
Look at that speed!
Dude, it looks cool too, doesn't it?
Let's put a andesite casing right there.
And then the rotation comes out right over here.
Oh!
I'm gonna need some gear boxes.
That's what a man needs.
I even have them!
That's fantastic.
I thought I was gonna make some.
Now.
Vertical gearbox goes in here.
Now we have this.
Maybe it'll be...
I like if we do it right here, actually.
Maybe with a mechanism where we open up from inside and can, you know...
Access the wheels here.
In a way.
But I need to see how this actually...
So why is it lying down like that?
Stop lying down!
Does it need to be put on a...
Oh, I see.
Okay.
So the rotation is gonna be that way, which means...
Let's bring this down.
Like that.
Vertical gearbox.
Can we not rotate that so that it's going...
There we go.
And then we need the gearbox to be this.
At least I think so, because these wheels are kind of big, right?
Woo!
Wait, will it hurt if I stand on it?
No.
Oh, man, it looks so scary, though, doesn't it?
Fuck me, that looks scary.
Oh, yeah, I guess I want them so that they're...
Going...
Against each other, sort of.
Which makes sense.
So you kind of want them like this, right?
Where this goes that way, this goes that way.
Right.
I do like him right here.
This looks kind of cool.
Let's see if we can't bring this down in a smart way.
In fact, we could bring this over one more.
Like that.
It's gotta...
We gotta have this spinning the other way, though.
We can probably put in something that reverses direction here.
It's not a problem, I think.
We can do that.
I believe that was the...
Something clutch?
No.
Gearshift?
Just a gearshift, I think.
Gearshift.
It may need redstone power.
But that's okay.
Let's plop that in right in between here.
And then we put in a little lever.
Just one.
Yeah!
Nice!
I'm gonna need more gearboxes.
Neat.
We may need another gearshift here.
Nope!
They're already spinning correctly.
Beautiful.
Wheels of destruction!
Now if I jump in...
I'm not gonna do it.
I feel like it's gonna damage me.
But wait a minute.
We have a problem.
We need a place for the output, too.
Right?
So we're gonna have to figure this...
You know what?
Actually, let me not have them spin right now.
I'm scared.
Okay.
They don't damage me right now.
Expect it.
I'm assuming they're just gonna drop the items.
We can just pick them up with, like...
A hobbit or something.
But, uh...
Let me just take another look at this.
See what they say here.
Oh, they're being processed.
And then they come...
Okay, so we can bring them with one of those.
Got it.
I may do that.
Let's see what makes sense.
We wanna bring them...
Oh!
We need a way to put items in on this side.
They go...
And they come up...
On the other side.
You know?
That would be lovely.
Which means the items will have to come down from up here.
Where this thing is.
Yeah!
I'm gonna grab that.
And we're gonna have a...
Make a little pooper up here that goes...
Right down there.
I guess that would be...
A...
Funnel.
Or something.
Yeah.
Funnel.
That would be the best.
Oh!
Or...
We...
Let me think.
I wanna...
I wanna make this...
Look nice!
We take something...
And it goes on a...
And it goes...
And then...
But in order to do that...
These are in the way.
What if we do like an airport?
Guys, I'm thinking of an airport terminal.
Right now.
Are you with me?
Oh my god.
How are we gonna do this?
Oh!
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Sehr gut.
Ich benötige mehrere...
Fabrikanten...
I can't speak German anymore.
I lost the ability.
I forgot it all.
I need...
Au!
That's what I need.
Give me this.
I need nine.
Nine!
Ich benötige mehr.
I look like such a madman having a shovel in the left hand and a pickaxe in the right.
Like a little kid going...
I'm ready to Minecraft!
You know, all excited.
Like a little kid at the table with a spoon in one hand and a fork in the other.
Ready to eat.
That's me.
And I'm ready to consume this airport.
So, watch this.
Are you ready?
It starts here.
And then...
But now...
Oh, wait.
No, no.
Not yet.
It is not yet time.
We go down like this.
Oh, I'm so excited, actually.
Where's my shovel?
Oh, there it is.
Will it work, though?
I don't know.
Let's...
Okay, so...
No!
The other way.
Oh, my God.
Let's see.
We're gonna cover it up, too!
Oh, my God.
Oh, that looks sick!
Okay, it's going down there, right?
It's going down?
Oh, wait.
This is insane.
And then...
We're gonna go horizontal for a bit.
And then we make a turn.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, where am I?
How am I not out?
I'm out.
Wait, where am I?
Yes, yes.
Let me calculate!
Oh, my God!
It's perfect!
Oh, no.
This was so weird.
The way this works.
Wait.
Fuck!
I need to see this again.
Okay.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh.
Oh!
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
That's how we do it.
Then we go up.
So, we're like...
Wait, is that too...
It's fine.
The question is how we're gonna wire all this up.
I have no idea.
We're gonna figure it out.
Give me a mess.
Give me that.
Silly boy.
Bring that up to...
Oh, man.
I guess...
This is a small one.
We'd be smalling.
Like that.
And then...
Here comes the big one.
Hup.
That should work.
It is wonderful!
We're gonna have to adjust the windows a little bit.
Give me.
Wait, shouldn't this just kind of work?
I can even maybe grab some rotation from here.
And bring it in.
You know?
Watch this.
Like that.
And...
Gearbox.
Boom.
Let's see which way it's rotating!
It's the wrong way.
Crap!
So we need a little reverser.
Somewhere.
Wait.
Will this even go up on that?
Actually.
Hold on.
This may not work.
Maybe it's too tight.
May have to go one further that way.
We'll see how it works.
It looks...
Man.
These wheels are really spinning, aren't they?
Ho ho ho!
I wanna try and crush something.
Oh my god!
It's so smooth!
Damn!
That looks sick!
Okay.
Let's bring in rotation from somewhere else.
Oh my god.
Now...
Now for the tough part.
This was the easy part, you know?
Now it's gonna become hairy.
This is gonna be a real pain in the butt.
I need some lights.
Aziz!
Light.
First off, we gotta test something here.
Proof of concept.
I'm gonna crank this shit.
I'm gonna get my grank.
Grand crank.
I think I left it out here.
Or not.
Oh!
I put it in the box.
Crank.
Proof of concept!
I'm gonna crank this shit.
Ah, wait.
It's not...
But is it because it's not running that it's not working?
Maybe it's because of that?
Let me test something here.
Wait a sec.
Ah, wait!
Still, it's one before.
There we go.
Now.
Connect these.
And then from here.
I'm gonna do this.
Do that.
Wait.
Uh...
This ain't gonna work.
Unless it can go like this.
Ah!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm an idiot.
You have to do it like this.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Connect these now.
Ah, but then this doesn't work.
Oh!
I almost touched it.
My ears are itchy!
Oh my god!
Ah!
I think there's something wrong with my ears.
Like it came out of nowhere.
Okay, so up.
Up.
Boom.
That's it now.
Okay.
Yes!
Wait, isn't this the same issue then?
Wait, what am I thinking here?
Start by doing that.
There we go.
And now we go up!
This was the plan.
Here, here.
There, there, there.
Eeeeee!
That's cutting it tight.
Let me have to go one further.
Hate to say it.
But it has to be done.
Oh my god!
I'm running out of space down here.
I'm losing my mind.
Lights!
And we connect these two.
Like that.
And now...
A little horizontal action.
Like that.
Beautiful.
And...
Now we go up.
From here...
To...
I guess that one works.
Is that too steep?
Maybe...
May have to be...
That one.
Too far?
Or...
Not aligned?
I don't want to calculate.
I just want to do.
You know?
Wait.
Why is...
One below?
Maybe it is too far.
See, that works.
So why wouldn't...
This one up here work?
Wait.
Something's wrong.
This one should work.
Here?
Oh, it does work.
Okay, good.
And there it is.
We have successfully...
Potentially maybe done it.
Let's crank this shit.
And see if I'm right.
Cranking time.
Item?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I guess you need some space here.
Uh...
Maybe this one needs to be running before this one goes over there.
You know?
See, it stops right there.
This one may have to run before it considers...
So maybe the other configuration I had did work.
And I just assumed it was because of the wrong thing.
Damn.
But you know what?
I just realized something.
This is kind of a...
overly complicated way to do this.
I mean...
There's a better way of doing this.
A fan, for example.
And some funnels.
Or, uh...
What are they called?
You know, the thingies.
But...
This is cooler.
I like this.
In fact...
I'm gonna stick with it.
We're gonna figure this out.
How hard can it be?
Just need some rotation.
We got some here.
Doesn't need to be fancy or fast or anything.
We put a little vertical...
Bastard in there.
And the world's our oyster.
Like that, you see?
Ah, but that's ugly.
I don't want that.
That's ugly.
Uh...
We wanna make it nice as...
Whoa!
Nice.
And...
Yeah.
We wanna make it nice.
We can, uh...
Bring it down from here, I guess.
Make it a little rugged.
Industrial looking.
Right?
I can get behind that.
Where's my vertical boy?
Found it.
Uh...
So that would be...
Probably here.
Hell yeah.
I need more gearboxes, man.
I'm running out.
And for that, we need cocks.
Just...
Make a lot.
Make like...
14.
And then we need to make gears.
That's good.
Tell me it's the right direction, please.
Yes!
Good shit.
At this point, I don't even wanna calculate.
I just rely on luck.
You know, I just go like, please.
I pray...
I play, uh...
Hope.
Craft.
That's what I do.
So that needs to spin the same direction.
Now, wasn't there a nice and really convenient way of doing this?
We saw that in one of the ponders.
I forgot which one.
Uh...
It may have been for...
Hmm...
You know how you relay in one direction?
Shit.
I mean, if I use two wheels, it's gonna go opposite, isn't it?
God, what was it called?
Was it Transmission or something?
Let me see.
Gear...
Uh...
No, it's not Gearshift.
There was one thing that could do this.
Could be the...
Clutch?
No.
Not that one.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
What is that one?
Mechanical Roller.
Bro.
We gotta make this as well.
But we need another crushing wheel to make it.
This is no easy process to make, you know?
This is gonna take a while and a lot of hand power.
But I wanna make it.
Redstone Contact.
Hopefully.
It's not Gearshift.
It was...
Do-do-do...
Oh, God.
Why am I blanking on this?
I know the name for it.
I know exactly what I'm looking for, too.
I'll know it when I see it.
Chain Drive!
That's it!
Encase Chain Drive.
I may actually have some.
I think I made a couple.
There it is.
Nuggets.
Let's make, uh, more.
Sink Nuggets and K-Zing.
Wonderful.
I've got it, brother.
Ah!
We gotta cook this first!
Yeah, burn it.
Too much copper.
Just throwing some of this away.
We don't need it right now.
Now,
I'll turn these into...
Nuggets.
And then...
Encase Chain Drive.
Thirteen of them!
Yeah!
That's it, baby!
Ah, wait.
No.
Ooh, hold on.
Uh...
Yeah, uh...
And then we...
Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine.
And then we do one of these.
It's...
Going the right way!
Beautiful!
And now, to continue the success...
We bring this guy.
Let's see here.
Like that.
And then we turn a Reno.
Boom.
Or we...
Yeah, we can do that too, I guess.
Like this.
And then a simple gearbox at the end.
This is looking a little messy.
But, uh...
It is what it is.
Yep.
I have a feeling, though.
Isn't that gonna be reversed?
Ah, shit.
I don't even have a gearbox.
Yeah, and...
But, gimme!
Uh, no.
Cock.
I should just make, like, a whole army of these.
Like, you...
You can never have enough gearboxes.
Casing.
I got so much of that.
Wait, what am I missing?
Oh, cock wheels.
Shafts.
And for shafts, we need this.
Cock wheel...
Make, like, half.
That's right.
Eight gearboxes.
Can't have enough of those.
This may spin the opposite way, though.
I can't think.
But, maybe it's okay.
Because, check it out.
We're gonna...
What am I gonna do?
I guess I can just reverse direction in between here.
Which is kinda hacky.
Not nice, but...
Yeah, no.
It is what it is.
Or...
Maybe I chain drive somehow.
Wait, even better.
What if I just put a...
Gearbox...
That's gonna do the same, isn't it?
Yeah.
But that isn't...
That was definitely an easier...
And more elegant way to do it.
Still wrong, though.
Still...
Shit.
I mean, we have rotation here.
Oh, what?
That hurt?
Somehow.
Why?
Also, isn't this spinning the wrong way?
Wait, why...
Why is this suddenly...
How...
Wait, how the hell?
Oh, it's because of this up here!
Ah!
I see.
So, we don't even need this anymore.
Which means I can use it down here!
Instead!
Oh my god.
Throw...
This away.
Put that back up there.
We're just gonna put a normal shaft in here.
For normal people.
And then...
Believe it or not...
We're gonna...
Up here and in there.
Maybe instead of this, we do a vertical.
Ah, but it can't do vertical and horizontal.
That's too bad, man.
That's too bad.
I guess I can bring this in.
Let me see what this looks like.
But then, isn't this gonna be reversed again?
It is!
That sucks.
Damn.
But let me just have a look.
Wrong way.
But if we turn it around again, then it's the right way!
So, so we turn again.
Uh...
Uh, shit.
So, oh no.
I gotta put this back, then.
If that's...
This is ugly, though!
I don't, I don't like the way it looks.
Like, I'm, I'm gonna put my foot down here and say no to this solution.
It's ugly.
I don't like ugly.
We're gonna have to figure this one out.
So, obviously, I did it there.
Why can't I do the same thing here?
You know?
Also, why are there...
No, that works.
That's fine.
I think it would be easier if we somehow just connect it.
I'm overthinking this.
Let me chain drive the shit out of this.
Why won't you turn?
Okay.
Are you turning the right way?
There we go.
And then a chain drive at the end here again.
Now it's turning that way, which means it should...
This should work.
Yeah!
And now it's the easiest chain drive in the universe.
Oh, fuck.
Easiest chain drive in the universe from the other side.
We're so close.
We're almost there.
Can you feel it?
I can smell the success coming.
I mean, we can just...
Oh, dude.
This is it.
We just grab from here.
Love grabbing.
Look at this.
And now...
For my next trick.
Fuck!
But it's okay!
It's okay, because we can reverse.
Like this.
And then...
Like that.
Boom!
Wait, it's crushing things it's not supposed to crush right now.
Yeah!
Look!
Oh!
Oh, you bastards.
Leave me alone.
In fact, just...
Make a day.
I also need food.
I believe I have steaks.
I don't have steaks.
What?
Man, where's all my food gone?
Did I really eat it all already?
I, uh...
Burn this!
This is looking kind of crazy.
Let's just fill up the floor again here to make it look nice.
Oh, no.
Nice.
And then...
We're gonna put a little cover on...
Like on this one here.
And then I'm gonna have some kind of mechanism that takes the items in there.
But wait, we also need to bring the items out!
Right?
We're not done!
There's only half of it.
Oh, at this point I must have a lot of wheat.
Yeah!
32!
We're gonna go feeding frenzy.
This farm is coming along nicely.
Look at this guy stuck up at my roof.
Nerd.
I wish they made it so that when animals have been fed and they don't want any more food, that they just stop following me.
So that way you can filter them out naturally, you know?
Like, who hasn't been fed?
Okay, everyone's been fed.
We're gonna have a lot of meat soon.
And life is gonna look good.
Okay.
Now here...
I do wanna kinda encase this a little bit.
Because it is a little ugly.
I admit it.
Do that one.
Then we're gonna...
Yeah, this is obviously temporary.
Items go in.
They get crushed.
They come out.
Don't fall in the fucking thing!
Don't!
Dude, I just wanna get through!
Okay, fine.
I'll walk this way.
Okay, so the items come here.
The items come there.
What happens then?
Let's brainstorm this one.
We go below!
Ah!
Oh!
Oh my god, dude!
We're gonna go in here!
We're gonna go up!
Where are we coming up, though?
Wait.
Oh my god.
You know what the best part is?
We can utilize this rotation!
Watch.
It's going the other way!
Oh, man.
Watch this!
Yeah!
Tell me this isn't incredible!
Now we go the other way.
Let me see.
One.
Two.
Oh, is it...
No, not yet.
Not yet.
Here.
Maybe.
And then...
Oh!
That way?
Yeah.
Yep.
And then from here, we're gonna grab this son of a gun.
No!
That's wrong.
Maybe we do a little...
Gearbox!
That's the wrong way!
One further.
I like one further.
Like that.
We figure out the rest later.
This is good now.
Wait!
We got a chain drive right here!
Can't we use that?
Chain drive.
Spinning that way.
Okay.
So on this side...
What's happening here, then?
Spinning that way.
Let's say we go one further.
This should turn the right way!
Like that?
Gearbox?
Fuck!
No.
I guess I was wrong.
No!
Yeah, it's because I looked at the bottom.
I fucking
hate that.
Alright, take me down!
Fuckin' rip my levels.
Unbelievable.
I hate that!
I'm missing items.
What's missing?
I think I got it all.
Ah, man.
That's a rough one.
I was like level 20.
That's like 13 levels down the drain.
Feels bad, man.
How do I prevent this from happening?
This is kinda sad, as the kids are saying.
I think we go up now, guys.
So if we go up now...
Wait a minute.
What if...
Thinking.
Wait.
I'm thinking.
So we go up.
But that's ugly.
That's...
That's a no bueno.
We actually hate that.
Hmm.
We can make a turn.
Into a burn.
Are we fanning?
Wait.
What does it take to...
Hold on.
Fan.
Encased fan.
Right.
Below.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I have a great idea.
That looks insane, by the way.
Wait.
Show me the vertical.
I guess that would be...
Puddle.
Or hose.
Or whatever it was called.
Shoot.
There it is.
But wait.
How do we get items in, though?
That's how.
So they go in.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh.
I know what to do.
I've got it.
Fixed inventory first.
The ideas are there.
The plan is in motion.
I can't be stopped now.
We're gonna decorate our house.
Like that.
Is that a ladder?
Oh, yeah, it is.
Sweet.
Throw all this crap away.
We don't need it.
Okay.
Here we go.
We are gonna...
Make a turn.
Right here.
No.
Very soon, we will turn.
Not yet.
How do I extend this easily?
Like, I need to...
Whoops.
Well, that's not what I wanted.
Damn it.
I guess what I wanna do...
Da-da-da-da.
Let's use this here.
One shaft there.
Now we connect.
Zzz.
Oh my god, I almost fell down again.
I don't wanna fall down.
I have nightmares of falling down.
Shaft here now.
Great.
And then these are gonna turn right there.
How far, you ask?
I'm glad you asked.
You see where I'm going with this?
It is so simple, it's stupid.
Um...
Yeah, I guess I would...
Do this.
Here.
Right.
And then over here.
I need to turn this bastard.
You see?
Right into that chest!
That's the plan, that's the vision.
If only you were...
There we go!
But is that gonna work?
Maybe if we use a funnel.
That's probably it.
I'm scared.
I don't know if this will work.
Let me try some things here.
Funnel time!
I must have it.
I got a brass funnel.
But what about andesite funnel?
Don't have it.
I'm okay with brass though.
And then...
And then we're gonna do...
Uh...
Chutes.
Didn't I have chutes on me?
Did I really put those away?
Whoops.
Wait, what?
Where did those come from?
I'm so confused.
Yeah!
And?
Oh my god!
It's perfect!
Let's see.
Please let it work.
First try.
Oh wait.
Shit!
Stop!
It's...
It's emptying.
Wait, what?
What just happened there?
Wait, does the...
Does that mean it's going the other way?
I'm confused.
I can't remove this.
I cannot remove this either.
Hmm.
We also need rotation from the bottom...
Oh wait, wait.
I have an idea.
Wait, don't fall down.
Don't fall down.
Oh man.
Oh man!
Shit!
Why is this such a pain?
Actually...
Better idea.
I got a better idea.
We simplify.
Forget this.
We're gonna bring it in via that way.
Much better.
Don't have to think about it too much.
I do wanna make sure I don't fall down and die now when I collect this.
Sweetness.
Okay, so we bring it to here and then from here...
In.
Got it.
There we go.
There.
And...
Then we go that way.
Into...
I...
You know what?
I could even take this rotation from there.
I don't really mind.
That's fine.
And then we also need one right here.
But the other way.
Hell yeah!
Funnel time.
Wait, does this work?
Ooh.
Uh...
Ah!
Wait!
I think we need to activate the fan first.
So how do we do this?
Maybe with the chain drive?
Oh yeah!
Yeah!
I...
In fact!
Check it out.
We're gonna do this.
What?
Fucking hell!
Why are you not turning the way I want you to turn?
You bastard!
Oh, it don't work like that, I guess.
Or what?
Hmm...
I see.
That's too bad.
I mean, that's fine too.
Uh...
The question is though, does it matter which way it spins?
We'll find out.
So what we need...
Oh god, this angle is confusing me.
I'm like tilting my head in real life, trying to understand.
So we're gonna do that...
And then we're gonna do a vertical.
Is it working?
Ah!
It went in!
Uh...
Let's double check.
This goes on.
Let's see what happens up there.
Uh...
Now to get out.
How do I get out?
I'm stuck in my own creation.
I have to found the exit.
Yeah!
Dude, are you ready?
Wait, wait, wait.
We're gonna make this extra special.
Holy shit.
It's happening.
Everyone calm down.
No,
I need more!
Uno mas!
Spruce is not it.
That's it.
Right there.
You ready?
We're gonna...
We're gonna cover up real quick.
Something nice.
Glass, maybe.
What can we make out of glass?
Paints.
They can't go horizontal, though.
Shit.
Uh...
Whatever.
Okay.
Let's just...
Let's just do it.
Let's see here.
Crush.
I mean, whatever.
Oh.
What was that?
Raw sink?
Let's try it.
I have it.
I had it.
Damn.
Let's try raw copper.
Watch.
Oh, hey!
You can see...
They're down there now.
Any moment.
I'm on.
Oh, that was fast!
Wait, what did I just do?
So, I put in raw copper?
I got crushed raw...
Oh, okay.
But what...
What's the point?
Hold on.
Show me the bounce!
The hell?
There's no bouncing?
Wait, what?
What's the point of this?
Crushed raw sink?
It's the fucking silly song again!
Oh!
Oh, that's why you do it.
To get nuggets of experience, I guess.
I didn't get any nuggets!
Are they down here?
Are you hiding from me?
Little nuggets...
Where art thou?
They're not there.
Let me try again.
And now I really want to see.
When it comes out, you know?
And...
In?
I thought it would be...
I thought when it said nugget of experience, I thought it meant the little things that fall on the ground that I collect.
But...
But I just threw in a bunch of...
Like, where is it?
Wait, there's something going on.
Where did my copper go?
Dude, am I...
I don't see anything moving along this.
Oh!
Oh, there it is!
Oh my god.
Wait, 49 nuggets of experience.
And I have...
I'm level 12.
Oh my god!
Dude!
This is insane!
Crush it all!
And...
Okay.
I wonder how much compared to just cooking it is, you know?
So now I have this.
I guess I can put that in here.
And do I get experience from...
Do I double dip?
Double didgeridoo?
I guess I would only know by destroying it.
But, uh...
If I destroy it, it's gonna contain experience from the other stuff I did.
So this is not a good test.
In fact, I need to destroy this first.
See?
There's all my experience.
And now we put it back.
Let's see.
I was gonna cook this now.
Let's just make it cook all four.
I mean, all four of the...
woods.
Okay, it has one more in it.
If I get experience now, this is...
This is gonna be wild.
I don't.
Okay, so the question then is...
Is it the same amount of experience I ended up getting or not?
You know?
But there was also something else.
Let me see here.
So copper...
Crushed raw copper.
I guess I can...
Turn them into nuggets.
I guess...
Oh wait, that's actually a way...
And then I can turn the nuggets into bars.
And I get clay out of it.
Or I can just blast it immediately and get a bar.
This is like the longer path, and you get some clay out of it too.
Yeah.
Sweet, dude.
Let me crush some more.
What about...
What if we crush some dirt?
We need a better insertion mechanism here.
It is not up to the standards right now.
Maybe scaffolding.
I like it.
And then we're gonna use...
Flapjacks.
Does it still work?
What if I crush wheat?
Yeah.
Dude, it's so sad.
I'm almost dirty!
Wheat flour.
Okay, so that works beautifully.
I can even make it so that I open, and then I throw it in.
Close it.
Or we put a little funnel here or something to make it...
This thing is a little distracting though.
Maybe we can make that look better.
You know, we can probably do like a gearbox up here.
Vertical gearbox into a bunch of...
Boxes down here, and then put it that way, you know?
That's probably better.
I do like being able to see what's happening out here, though.
It's cool.
Very cool.
Uh...
What now?
Let me see what else I can crush.
Dude, I'm in a crushing mood.
I'm gonna crush everything, man!
I guess...
Okay, so if crimpside is easy to mine...
It's like...
Super nice chance of getting iron, you know?
In other words...
With my digging machine, I'm just gonna dig whatever...
I find a bunch of random shit in the mountain, right?
Before...
All of that, or most of it, was just throwaway material that I don't need.
Now...
I throw it all in the crushing wheel, and I actually get something out of it.
Right?
That's the whole deal.
Blaze rods turn into way more blaze powder, which is awesome.
Same with the bones.
Isn't this just like...
Like a really nice thing to do?
Cobblestone into gravel.
Cocoa beans into dye.
Right.
This thing is crazy.
From now on, we need to only have Silk Touch.
I was slandering Silk Touch today at the start.
And then, uh...
I had to change my mind now.
Let's make endstone powder, dude!
I have endstone.
Let's see it.
Dude...
Ha ha ha!
Let's see what comes out.
Show me the goodies!
Uh, let me fix my inventory while we wait for that.
Put this stuff in here.
And all this crap can go in there.
Don't really need this right now.
All the wood.
And this thing, and that thing.
Oh, yeah.
Wonderful.
Okay, let's see.
Wait a minute!
Lies!
And stone.
Oh, wait.
Really?
Out of all the ones I threw in?
Not a single one of them?
I mean, I get there's a chance, but...
That seems extremely unlikely.
Say...
Come on.
It's gotta work.
It's like it's being halved every time.
Yeah, look!
Well, taking the 4.5, but...
Maybe it's rounding down.
Uh...
Wait a minute.
And...
Endstone powder.
Notice there's no percentage on this.
To me, that means it's guaranteed.
Also makes sense that 50...
If every one of them has a 50% chance...
Of coming back out as endstone...
That would statistically mean I would get half, which is what I'm getting.
So where is my powder?
What?
Hello?
What the fuck is happening?
This shit is bugged, bro.
Uh...
Can I have that, please?
Huh?
It's stuck in some sort of weird loop here.
Like, why is it going back up into the thing?
I can't even take it.
Okay, dude.
Yeah, it is...
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me try and stop this rotation.
Is it still doing that thing?
Wait, what the fuck?
Now I got it!
I don't understand nothing.
We gotta try that again.
This makes no sense.
Wait, let me see what...
Okay, hold on.
Shit!
Oh my god!
I don't understand!
Hold on.
Remove this.
What if I manually put it on?
I mean...
Okay.
I rest my case.
Your Honor?
Shit's on fire, yo.
Like, what is happening here?
This is bugged.
Either that, or it's...
Something...
Really...
Really unintuitive is going on here.
That makes absolutely no sense.
Bro, what is going on?
Huh?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Have I found, like, a gravitational anomaly right here?
Localized entirely within my house?
Or is it also over here?
It's floating!
Interesting.
Maybe it's, like, otherworldly, exotic...
Like, it's coming from...
The weirdest place of all time.
Maybe it just simply has, like, anti-gravity powers.
Maybe that's just what's happening here.
I still don't understand why I was going up...
Oh, actually...
Oh, wait a minute.
I understand.
I think.
When this was spinning...
Watch.
Hold on.
No, actually, no.
I was about to say...
If they were spinning the other way, it would make sense.
That maybe it's, like, attracted to the wheels, you know?
So if I put it close to it, it gets sucked in.
Or not?
Oh, but maybe it's because it's, like, anti-gravity.
That's why it's going up.
So if I were to reverse this direction and put it here, they're going to fall down?
Wait.
There's no way.
Um...
Give me anti-reversal!
I mean, actually, just reversal.
I need a gear shift.
If I have it.
I don't think I have it.
I...
Okay, well...
Uh, let's just not think about it too much.
Let's just utilize it.
So, why...
I guess the only way we can put them on the thing is if they get thrown down with enough force.
So what I think we need to do is to have this be higher.
In other words, we're simply going to put this...
Um...
Let me see.
So one, two...
Three.
Ooh, that's a little too close!
Ah, but...
Of course, the rotation came from here.
Damn it.
This is also way too...
That ain't good, bruh.
Unless we...
Or we saw...
Oh, okay.
I have a better idea.
What if we funnel it into a funnel?
Or even a chute?
So that it's...
You know, it's forced.
Yeah, actually, I like that.
Take me on a ride!
Ooh!
Ooh, I almost fell on the wheels!
I still haven't tested whether or not that's going to damage me, but I assume it will.
Iron.
Not the material I want to spend...
My iron on, but whatever.
Right?
And then?
Boom.
I'm like 99% sure this will work.
You ready?
Wait, I didn't see, I didn't see.
Yes!
Totally fixed.
Boom, baby!
That's it.
Cover it up!
And call me...
New Hampshire.
We're done here.
Fixed.
Bug has been fixed.
Next!
Let's see what else we can make.
I'm about to crush everything.
Dude, I've been crushing it today.
I guess we can do that.
If you want string...
Hey, that's easy!
We just throw it in there.
Nice.
Bones.
Ow!
We get green dye from Cactus.
Charcoal.
None of these are exciting.
I want exciting.
Gandalf.
Exciting.
These ones are super exciting.
Silk touch.
Supremacy.
Boring.
Exciting.
Kind of exciting.
Boring.
I want fresh.
What's this?
Cinderflower.
Now that's interesting.
Netherrack.
Throw it in!
Come on!
Is it going to take the whole stack before it comes, or what?
Oh!
Oh.
What is that?
Cinder...
Flower.
Oh, wait.
Cinderflower.
Compacting.
Blazecake base.
Okay.
Filling by spout.
What?
Potion of night vision and cinderflower becomes glowstone dust.
Potion of harming.
I have never heard of that.
Becomes gunpowder.
Potion of harming.
Potion of strength.
Oh.
Yo!
This is cool as hell.
Really dig that.
What else can I crush?
We keep crushing.
Dude, the crushing wheel is kind of...
Amazing.
Obsidian!
Yes, sir!
I don't have any.
But I can go get some.
I need food.
Oh!
Let's go feed the animals.
Before I forget.
I think it's time soon to slaughter them all, guys.
It's going to be an event to remember.
No, wait.
A night to remember.
Or something.
Look at the flock!
I prioritize cow.
Sorry, sheep.
Your meat is just not as delicious.
There you go.
Enjoy.
Man, we need a bigger farm up here with the windmill.
It's just too slow with the wheat.
I guess I gotta eat these for now.
Which sucks.
Okay.
I do want to get a little bit more experience, just to enchant my pickaxe.
I'm gonna go mine this obsidian.
Dude, we should try and throw crying obsidian there, too.
And obviously...
I'm just gonna take one more.
We're also gonna try and throw sheep in there.
Or animals.
Maybe that's a good test, you know, before I jump in.
Maybe we can call up Stuart.
Have him do a little field test.
I don't know why I took this path.
What was I doing?
Oh, yeah.
Man, the crushing wheel must be really strong if it can crush obsidian.
Let's see.
I'm so ready.
There it is.
Let me also throw this in while I'm at it.
Wait, was this like a chance thing?
Wait a minute.
Obsidian.
Powdered obsidian.
Okay, so I got lucky.
I got both of my obsidians back.
Neat.
Okay, I expected this from the achievement.
Sturdy sheet.
Oh!
Lava?
Oh, okay.
Powdered obsidian with lava.
Process and press.
Okay, so it's like a sequence.
Okay.
I guess we could do that at some point.
But first, I need to crush.
You thought I was done crushing?
Oh, boy.
You're wrong.
We're gonna crush till the days...
Uh, I couldn't figure something out.
Boring.
Wait, do some of them give more?
Oh, it's because it's a block of raw copper.
Got it.
I like this, because fox saddles.
Am I right?
Short grass into wheat seeds.
Way more sugar.
Oh!
Way tough is like the best thing ever to destroy them.
You get so much out of it.
Tough, tough.
Oh, I have a lot!
Yo!
A once useless block has now become mainstay.
I mean, this is obviously kind of janky the way they jump up there.
We gotta make some kind of more neat way to do it, you know?
Give me that.
Give me these.
Are you cooking something?
You're not.
Okay.
Look at all this!
And a bunch of flint!
That's a neat way to get a bunch of arrows, too.
Like, this may be the premier way to get arrows.
If you think about it.
Put these in here.
I kind of want to do this powdered obsidian thing, actually.
Because I think it may lead to train stuff.
But we need lava for that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
What was that?
That was something new.
Use sturdy sheets to create a casing for railway components!
The locomotive age!
Praise Jesus!
We have done it!
Well, not yet, but...
Almost.
Almost!
I fucking knew it was connected here!
A new gauge!
Okay.
Okay, we're doing this right now.
Or as soon as possible.
I really need food.
Like, food surely...
is around the corner.
I'm not gonna feed them yet.
Uh, first we empty.
I guess cinderflower...
Is that food or not?
It doesn't feel like food to me.
Like, would you eat that?
I think it's more like a metal.
Even though it's not metal.
Know what I'm saying?
Put this over here.
I don't need glue.
I don't need glass.
I don't need obsidian, actually.
Oh, wait, we can just keep...
Uh, hold on.
Hold on.
We can just keep going like this?
And if we get it back, we just keep going?
Genius.
Ah-ha!
We got them both!
Yo!
Infinite item discovered.
I will.
At some point, we're gonna get unlucky and lose them, but, you know.
It's kind of sweet that way.
Uh, let me see here.
So, what did it say?
Sturdy?
One powdered obsidian becomes one sturdy sheet.
Okay.
So, we need to extract from lava.
And I guess we can do that from that over there.
Or we bring lava over to the factory.
That's probably a better way.
I need a bucket.
Okay, we got one of them back.
Um, what did I just...
What did I just say?
Bucket!
Empty it.
Let's go get some lava.
I'm not actually sure if it works the same way as water, where you can make infinite lava.
Yeah, I don't think...
Wait, I don't think you can.
Because look at...
Look at the way this is not sort of...
You know what I mean?
Wait.
So, we need to continuously provide lava?
Hmm.
Really?
Okay, well, we need a spout.
And what was it?
Powder...
What's that?
Black concrete powder.
That's also interesting.
Okay.
Can I not just manually fill this bastard up with a bucket?
I feel like that should be possible.
Do I have one of these things?
Spout!
I have it.
And then we needed one of those...
depots.
Oh, this is probably going to require some sort of...
Or not.
Yeah, no power for this.
I guess it's just...
Actually, I'm going to do manual labor, guys.
I'm going to be manual labor mark.
Here we go.
I'm going to plop this one down right here.
This is hella scuffed, I understand.
But okay, bear with me.
Hoi!
Crap cake-o!
Don't work like that, huh?
Okay.
Shit.
How do I...
Do I really got to use pipes?
My brother just wants to do manual labor.
We're not at automation stage yet.
Fine.
Let's do it.
I'm going to go back here.
Expand my factory.
I guess we're bringing in water.
We can also bring in lava.
It's not a big deal.
So we have one here.
We can have one here.
And let's send me one more here.
So, depot.
One of these.
Oh, not like that.
Hello, guys.
Dude, I actually...
I was not expecting to do any of this today.
I was going to go to the nether and shit and start digging.
Whoops.
Do not plant those.
Stop planting!
Just eat!
Now, we are going to do this.
Actually, wait, spout.
I need to see something.
from the side.
Okay.
I see.
And then we need the little...
Yep.
Okay.
I can make it.
I can do it.
And I hate this little situation I've got going on here with random shit everywhere.
I need, like, a proper workshop, you know?
Or factory.
We gotta encase the factory in walls at some point.
Soon.
Because right now, it doesn't feel good.
What did I just say?
Uh...
Right.
I need these things.
Not that one.
Fluid pipes.
Anything fluid-related is what I need right now.
Maybe a fluid valve?
Barrels, huh?
I can make those.
It is, of course, the one and only...
Slap.
Two barrels.
I wanna make more.
You think I'm done?
No way.
Okay, fine.
I may be done.
Wait, how do I make, uh...
Isn't it...
Yeah!
Crack a barrel!
It's a place you can eat, apparently.
Always wanted to go.
Now.
Fluid.
Copper sheets.
Easy.
Let's make...
Four.
And...
And we also need the little, uh...
Pump.
Pipe and cogwheel.
Man, that's so cheap to make!
It's kind of crazy.
Make them both.
Pump.
Is that everything?
So I have this, I put lava in there.
And we have the pump.
And just to confirm here, I can just fill this up manually, right?
Shit!
Can I really not do that?
Well, how the hell are they...
Wait a sec.
Spout.
How is the lava getting in there?
Do I need to pump it out of a lava lake?
I can't manual labor this?
That's kind of unbelievable.
Shit.
Maybe I need the fluid valve.
Whatever it was called.
Valve pipes help control fluids propagating through pipes.
The shaft input controls where the fluid is currently.
No, that's not really what I need.
Fluid.
Portable fluid interface.
Don't think I've made this.
That kind of sounds like what I need, doesn't it?
Copper casing.
I got one.
Portable.
Let's make it over here.
Shoot.
Shit.
I don't think I can make more.
I can make one.
Oh, fluids.
Let's ponder on it.
What is this?
Fluid tanks on moving contraptions cannot be accessed by any pipes.
Oh, that's what that is.
Okay, I see what it is.
This is like the thing I have at my windmill just with fluids.
Yeah, it's going to empty us.
Yeah, okay.
It's not what I need.
Oh,
spruce stuff.
How do I...
There must be a way to manually put fluids inside something.
Like some kind of opening or whatever.
Maybe, maybe this one actually.
Maybe the item drain.
I've yet to find a use for it.
This has to be it.
Put it on top maybe?
Lava?
Ah!
Lava is in there!
Okay.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Oops.
Did I just get rid of the lava?
Lava?
Shit!
Okay, fine.
I'm going to get more lava.
Okay, well, now we can have lava in that.
So maybe we can take the lava from that via a pipe.
To bring it into the spout.
That's maybe how to do it.
Or maybe even...
Yeah, just a simple pipe, I guess.
Let's see how that works.
In fact, let me let gravity do the work.
Because otherwise we probably need the pump.
Let's say we do this, right?
And we put the drain on top.
And then we do this.
And lava.
What?
Really?
I am so surprised.
Can I grab this lava again?
Fuck.
I can't even grab it.
Huh?
Wait.
Item drain.
We got to ponder this.
Let's try to understand.
They can extract fluids from items.
Okay.
Yes.
Right click.
It's a poor fluids.
Got it.
Pipe networks can now pull the...
Okay, so we do need a pump.
But, you know what that means?
We probably don't need this one then.
Maybe it's okay.
Gonna have to go get more lava though.
One last lava run.
Ah, no.
Zombies do not want me to get this lava.
Here, you like lava?
Fuck you.
You're dead, son.
You like lava?
Okay.
I'm out.
So let me build it...
Actually, right here.
No.
Go back to the factory.
And we do have that thing.
Ah, I probably am gonna need some stuff.
Like wheels, you know?
I'm gonna grab stuff like this and that.
And, you know.
Something like...
God, I don't know.
Like...
Half of these, you know?
Bit of everything.
Ugly.
Ugly, ugly.
I guess this would be endstone powder in there.
Fine.
I believe.
Trust.
We got this.
I'm gonna be spouting so much right now, dude.
Wait.
Oh, right.
This is the spout from before.
I thought I had duplicates.
So, we basically want to put the item drain...
There.
Uh...
Pipe.
Oh my god.
No!
I can't even sprint.
Okay, you know what?
Stop.
Get some help.
Don't be a bitch.
Just get it done.
That was the monster today.
What are you doing, man?
Grab this too.
No.
Leave it.
Da-da-da-da.
I need pipes.
Which means I need this.
Pipe me up, Scotty!
Give me 28 pipes.
Da-da-da-da.
We also need wheels.
Cogs!
Okay, so the way we connect this now...
Is...
Maybe it's better if we move this...
To here.
Because then we're gonna do this!
And...
Wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey!
Even better.
We're gonna utilize this rotation we have here.
That's right.
Just like that.
We're gonna go like this.
Because then we do that...
And we wheel it!
See that?
It's a little ugly.
I get it.
What are you doing?
Eh.
Good enough!
That's your work!
Uh...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We also need belts and stuff.
But maybe we do it manually.
No, no, no, no.
Set it up.
Do it properly.
I gotta go back and get more stuff.
And I can't sprint.
Don't worry about it.
My diet is...
Only berries.
And you know what?
It's...
Fantastic.
Fascinating.
Now.
What I need...
Is wheels.
Probably.
Maybe not.
Actually, I don't.
Uh, what was it?
It was pressing, right?
Powder.
Uh, yeah.
Two presses.
Do I even have that?
May have to make it.
Oh, god.
That costs a lot!
I may have to cannibalize.
We're gonna cannibalize a little bit.
I need more...
Everything.
That's...
Wait, that's sink ingots.
Don't like that.
Oh, we just learned something new.
Whatever.
I'm busy.
We gotta make...
Me...
Uh...
Alloy?
And decide.
Do I have any?
I do!
Oh, my god.
Sweet.
Shaft time.
Let me try and think.
And then we need, uh...
Belts.
Got him.
Shafts.
And we got that.
Maybe a chest could be nice.
Uh, I don't need these.
Or that.
No.
What was it?
What did I just say?
Shaft.
Belts.
Uh, chest.
Chest time.
Just one.
And maybe from the beginning.
We need to...
Maybe we have another chest at the begin...
Yeah, actually, another chest.
Another chest.
And then we need a, um...
Maybe funnel time?
Guys, is it funnel time?
Huh?
Always loved funnel time when I was a kid.
But can I not make a normal funnel for normal people?
Kelp and...
Oh, that's easy.
Oh my god.
That's like super easy.
20 funnels!
That's a lot.
I've actually never had funnel cake.
I heard it taste like ass.
I lied.
I have never heard that.
But I'd love to try it.
Hmm.
Wait.
So it starts...
Wait, hold on a minute.
How does it work if I...
If I just start here and...
That's not going to automatically move that way, is it?
Ah!
We don't need depots when we do the belt!
Almost forgot.
In fact...
We go from here...
To, say, here.
That's why belts are so cool.
Right?
We're even going to utilize the rotation from here...
To there.
Beautiful.
Now, here, we're going to have a little chesty.
Like that.
Funnel time.
Ah!
Maybe too close.
Don't think that's going to work.
I'm going to have to extend these pipes a bit.
Put this guy here.
Yeah, I like that more.
Let's test.
Works.
Nice.
Okay, so you guys...
And then we need to press that shit.
I'm going to steal and cannibalize.
Do I only have one?
But I guess I have one at home.
Fine.
Cannibalization!
It's coming to your town.
Before you think.
So I can grab the one next to my house.
And we should be good to go.
I'm so ready.
Are you ready?
I do wonder, though, how much lava I'll need.
It's probably going to be some bullshit.
Like...
Oh, you can't just do one bucket.
You need...
A whole lake.
Give me this thing.
God, these berries are starting to taste...
Sour!
Don't look at this.
Don't worry about that.
Different times.
Here we go!
Are you ready?
Oh, wait.
We still need rotation.
It's fine.
Watch me rotate.
Oh, I wish I had chain drives.
Not that lucky.
I was one of those kids that was born without them, you know?
Like, I had funnel time.
But...
Oh, right.
Chain...
Shit.
What is in that box, anyway?
Oh, I had this already.
That's crazy.
Man.
I mean, I could hand-crank it.
I can crank that shit.
You know what?
Yeah.
Why not?
Lava time.
Boink!
Oh, wait.
We need input...
Uh...
Powder.
Oh!
Sploosh!
Unprocessed obsidian sheet.
Whoa!
All right.
Uh...
Wait.
Why are they different?
Huh.
Okay, maybe the hand crank is a bad idea.
Let's automatic crank instead.
Stop jumping on that.
And to wait...
And the way to do that is to...
Hmm.
If only I had two wheels.
Never mind, I have two wheels.
I have four in...
Oh!
Four in wheels.
Hey, it's not pretty, all right?
Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
Oh my god!
It's incredible!
We stopped there.
Ended on a...
Freaking banger of a cliffhanger!
Next time, I cannot wait to see what we're gonna do with that.
It's gonna be...
Pure cinema.
Dude, I felt good before starting this stream.
I feel even better now.
Pure back.
I had to go hug Jackie in celebration.
And...
I got a drink.
Cheers.
Yes!
Incredible.
Ah.
Man.
Hey, Teflon!
I made a working creative music resource pack.
Awesome, man!
I'm gonna grab that.
Thank you so much!
I think I may not have installed the...
The one I was supposed to install.
Correctly.
I...
I would...
I will have to check what I actually did wrong there.
But thank you.
I'm gonna try and get that installed.
And actually have it working.
I'm not drinking either.
I'm still drinking...
This is my second Foxy Condi.
With lemonade.
It's basically like a Danish version of a Sprite.
But in my opinion, a little better.
Oh yeah, the reverb was me.
I can do that with my mouth.
People don't believe me when I say that, but I can.
It's the same way I can do the...
The...
The drop, you know?
You hear that?
With my mouth.
Is Jackie was sent by CyberLife?
I don't know, but you were definitely not sent by the grammar people.
That was such a terrible comeback.
Holy shit, I suck.
I tried.
How do I be as cool as you?
I'm not that cool.
I wish I was as cool as you.
What do you say to that?
And I don't even know you.
Big move today.
Skull!
Does that fake Sprite have sugar in it?
It doesn't.
It's zero calories.
It probably has some other bullshit that's not good for you.
You know, like everything else in this world.
Anything you do, man, it's kind of bad for you.
Why is all the good stuff bad for you?
You know?
It's one of the oldest unsolved questions in math.
Oh.
I really needed this, man.
The last couple of Minecraft streams have been...
Like me gasping for air, you know?
Frustrated.
Down on my luck.
Beaten up.
Rough times.
Rock bottom.
But now we're back.
And it was all to get to the trains.
And I think we're there, guys.
The trains are here.
Next time will be the train episode.
And this one's confirmed, finally.
I know I keep saying it, but next time...
...is the train episode.
The chapter name for this episode should now be...
...Escalating Excitement.
You are so right.
I will name it that.
Thank you, G-Game.
How do you find the motivation to do everything on your own?
I've never find this much patience to figure all this stuff out.
I don't know.
I enjoy the process of it.
I know people get mad and think I'm rage baiting and stuff, you know?
But I'm legitimately just having fun figuring it out.
It's just, I like it.
I like the slow burn of it, you know?
It's fun for me.
I'm what you call a pleasure delayer.
You know?
When the pleasure finally comes, it's just so much better.
A patient gamer, yeah.
Everything is that much more sweet if you wait longer, you know?
The rage baiting part is you being completely blind sometimes.
Yeah, but I would argue that if you were to stream yourself playing the game and doing the same way I'm doing it, you would probably also be seen as blind, you know?
In your own way.
When you look at someone else's gameplay, it's easy to spot the things that the person playing isn't seeing.
That's my argument anyway.
Could be wrong, but I feel like that's the case.
And when you play on your own, you don't even notice these things.
But if you have someone watching you, you'll suddenly...
You'll suddenly realize how much stuff you're supposedly not doing right, you know?
Have you seen the next game?
Poll results.
I have.
It looks like Five Nights at Freddy's is winning.
But who knows what could happen.
There could be a guy from Finland who comes along.
You never know.
Let me actually find the poll here.
Here, you can vote on it there if you haven't yet.
The next game for the stream, you can vote on it.
The vote ends in like one day and 20 hours.
But it's looking like a Five Nights at Freddy's landslide.
But I did say if the game is very short, like if the winning game is super short, then I'm just gonna jump into the second most voted game on the list, you know?
After that.
So we'll see how it goes.
Fitting for Halloween coming up.
Yeah, actually.
I guess so.
I want RimWorld so bad.
One day.
One day it'll happen.
At some point, by the way guys, this will happen.
But at some point I'll make a poll.
And I will announce it like beforehand in like a secret video that I upload later.
that it's like a random, like it's like the last on the poll that wins.
Or like it's the one in the middle or something, you know?
Just to switch it up a bit, I guess.
To give the games a chance that aren't the, you know, always number one.
But maybe I'll think of something else.
Maybe that's a bit boring.
Maybe there's a better way of doing it.
But it could be fun, you know?
I realize it's not the one people want to watch, obviously, then.
But that's okay.
So many of the games in this poll are the ones I've been waiting for a long time.
Really?
Well, that's good.
I try to switch it up a little bit every time I do the polls.
See where people are, you know?
I honestly thought that, uh...
I didn't really think that Five Nights at Freddy's would be at number one.
Let's say that.
Because I googled the game and I saw a screenshot of it and...
Boy, the...
It looks bad.
I'm not gonna lie.
Like, that screenshot made it look like...
Something really bad, you know?
Like a terrible game.
But I'm ready to have my mind changed.
I am.
I have an open mind.
I thought for sure Hades 2 would win or something.
The Long Dark will be amazing too.
I'm not even sure what it is.
Like, not really.
But it seemed interesting.
Yeah, so it's a rank poll where you can put them in, like, a specific order.
But if you go into, like...
And you can't do this, but I can.
There's, like, a vote analytics I can look at.
It's a landslide for Five Nights at Freddy's in there.
Like, it's not even close.
Like, the number of people who put Five Nights at Freddy's as their number one...
Is...
Over three times...
More than any other game.
And while it doesn't look like it from the results...
It's simply because a lot of people chose different games for their number two.
You know?
So, it is...
It is vastly more popular than anything else on the...
On the list right now.
Last stream you said maybe we could add, uh...
Blueprints music to the Minecraft soundtrack.
Well, you did that?
Are there any other songs you would want to see?
I don't know if I'm gonna do it, though, Teflon.
It was just a thought, you know?
I think it is kind of weird to have that music during Minecraft.
Perhaps I'll just end up playing it myself.
With my music player.
Have some control over it during certain...
Moments in the game.
Just like I did with the Sims music in the first season.
That was quite fitting for when I was building, you know?
But I appreciate it anyway.
Talos music also...
Like, so many good music tracks are fitting.
In Minecraft.
Because Minecraft...
Spans so many different genres in a way.
Depending on what you do in the game.
Any music could work, you know?
You're building a house.
It's Sims music.
You're out there just...
Slowly exploring the world.
I would say that...
Blueprints or Talos works well.
If you're in combat, you know?
You would put on some...
Something else.
You think you'll ever play with shaders again?
I think I'll give it a try when the official shaders come out.
Apparently, Mohang or Mojang...
Is working on the official implementation for Java, but it's taking forever for some reason.
But when that comes out...
Definitely, I'm gonna try it.
But...
Dude, I tried to pronounce it right.
I thought it was...
Everyone always criticizes me when I say Mojang.
So I was like, is it Mohang?
I don't know.
How do you record games like Detroit Become Human?
Do you record one day or do you binge record, then upload, spread out?
Totally depends on the game.
For Detroit Become Human, it's totally like every day...
Or every second day, I record an episode.
And then I upload it the same day.
So it's whenever I feel like it, really, with that game.
Other games, I record a lot of and then spread it out.
It really depends.
Will you play Slime Rancher ever?
I will.
I will play it in 7,890 hours.
I don't know.
The name doesn't sound like something I would enjoy.
Slime?
Like, what is it?
You're a rancher with slime?
Like, what is that even?
What's the rest of your day looking like?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll play some Deadlock at some point.
I have one episode left to go.
Of Tokyo Vice.
It's what I'm watching right now.
So that's the finale.
I think I'll watch that.
At some point, I'll go for a walk.
Maybe I'll go for a long walk, actually.
There's a store that's quite far away from me.
But it's a store that I really like going to.
Because it's big and there's all kinds of selections.
But it's kind of far away, you know?
So it's kind of a trip to go there.
Maybe I'll do that.
I've not played Baba Is You.
It's on my list already.
CO preferences.
Many people have recommended it.
It's funny.
Like, all these games that you guys are recommending...
Like, I've played almost none of them, right?
But...
I recognize all the names.
Because everyone keeps mentioning them.
Touch Grass.
Well, it's just going for a walk, you know?
Some fresh air.
Really does wonders for me, sometimes.
You want to see the backlog?
Oh, I got you.
Feast Your Eyes.
It's right there.
Specifically made just for you.
You can check it out.
I actually did some more ranking the other day on the backlog.
So, some of the recent games are being ranked now, too.
Obviously, more samples need to be put in.
But, yeah.
The more rankings I do, the more accurate things are going to get.
And the more they're going to reflect my taste.
But, yeah.
Over time, it's going to get better and better with the rankings in there.
My personal rankings, that is, of course.
It's more like an enjoyment.
How much I enjoyed the game.
For example, Doki Doki Literature Club...
Wasn't a huge fan of the game itself.
But the streaming of it was actually kind of fun, you know?
So, I did get some enjoyment out of that, for sure.
I want to start my own channel and do blind playthroughs.
But instead of games, I'm going to do Excel, Blender, or AutoCAD Blind.
Go for it!
Sounds fun.
Plus, you learn things at the same time.
Excel, though?
That's maybe...
Hmm.
Blender, I can...
I don't know if people want to watch Excel.
But as long as you're having fun doing it, then I think it's good.
I think Blender could be something interesting.
Isn't AutoCAD kind of Blender, but for engineers?
That's how I understand it.
Would you rate based on stream experience or game experience?
It would be my enjoyment of playing the game.
And if that happened to be a game I streamed, and the streaming of it impacted my enjoyment, then yes, it would be part of it.
It's simply how much I enjoyed playing the game.
You know?
It's not like a ranking of...
Like, an objective ranking of how good the games are, you know?
That's not how to...
How I do that.
People watch EVE, spreadsheets aren't that far off.
Okay, yeah, I see that.
I mean, it's the same with World of Warcraft at times.
Like, if you go into raiding and stuff, there's a lot of spreadsheets there, too, regarding who is on what assignments and loot and all that.
Especially, I mean, I guess as a player you don't really look at that too much.
You just check out your assignments, right?
And then you go, but...
I guess the people organizing the events and stuff.
Guys, I'm out of here!
Thank you for watching.
This was a fantastic episode of Minecraft.
We are back, baby!
And I'm not afraid to say it.
It's real.
The train is coming!
I'll see you next time.
Bye-bye.